{
  "uniqueId": "JLPT N3",
  "name": "JLPT N3 Reading Quiz",
  "article": "a",
  "instructions": "Type the reading of the below word in Hiragana!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "IMAGE",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "JISHO_QUESTION_WORD",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "NONE",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "QUESTION_AND_ANSWER_LINK_QUESTION",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "answerCompareStrategy": "CONVERT_KANA",
  "compileImages": true,
  "cards": [
    {"meaning":"love","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"愛","answer":["あい"]},
    {"meaning":"love, affection","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"愛情","answer":["あいじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"sign, signal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合図","answer":["あいず"]},
    {"meaning":"to love","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"愛する","answer":["あいする"]},
    {"meaning":"companion, partner, company","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相手","answer":["あいて"]},
    {"meaning":"lamplight, light (in general), brightness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明かり","answer":["あかり"]},
    {"meaning":"room, time to spare, emptiness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"空き","answer":["あき"]},
    {"meaning":"obvious, evident, clear","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明らか","answer":["あきらか"]},
    {"meaning":"to dawn, to become daylight","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明ける","answer":["あける"]},
    {"meaning":"to give, to present, to award","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"与える","answer":["あたえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be hit, to be successful, to be equivalent to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当たる","answer":["あたる"]},
    {"meaning":"gathering, meeting, assembly, collection","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"集まり","answer":["あつまり"]},
    {"meaning":"to hit, to apply a patch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当てる","answer":["あてる"]},
    {"meaning":"not very (used as adverb), not much","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"余り","answer":["あまり","あんまり"]},
    {"meaning":"error","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"誤り","answer":["あやまり"]},
    {"meaning":"new, fresh, novel","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"新た","answer":["あらた"]},
    {"meaning":"to express, to show, to reveal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表す","answer":["あらわす"]},
    {"meaning":"to show, to indicate, to display","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現す","answer":["あらわす"]},
    {"meaning":"embodiment, materialization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現れ","answer":["あらわれ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to appear, to come in sight, to become visible, (2) to express oneself","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現れる","answer":["あらわれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be, to have","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"有る","answer":["ある"]},
    {"meaning":"to join together, to be opposite, to face, to unite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合わせる","answer":["あわせる"]},
    {"meaning":"memorization, learning by heart","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暗記","answer":["あんき"]},
    {"meaning":"stability, equilibrium","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"安定","answer":["あんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"unexpected, surprising","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"意外","answer":["いがい"]},
    {"meaning":"breath, tone","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"息","answer":["いき"]},
    {"meaning":"living thing, animal","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生き物","answer":["いきもの"]},
    {"meaning":"doctor, physician","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"医師","answer":["いし"]},
    {"meaning":"intention, purpose","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"意思","answer":["いし"]},
    {"meaning":"consciousness, senses","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"意識","answer":["いしき"]},
    {"meaning":"ago, since, before, previous","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"以前","answer":["いぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"greatness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"偉大","answer":["いだい"]},
    {"meaning":"(sl) to embrace, to hug, to harbour, to entertain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"抱く","answer":["いだく","だく"]},
    {"meaning":"to receive, to take food or drink (hum)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"頂く","answer":["いただく"]},
    {"meaning":"pain, ache, sore, grief, distress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"痛み","answer":["いたみ"]},
    {"meaning":"place, situation, position, location","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"位置","answer":["いち"]},
    {"meaning":"all at once","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一度に","answer":["いちどに"]},
    {"meaning":"(the) market (as a concept)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"市場","answer":["いちば","しじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"best, first, number one","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一番","answer":["いちばん"]},
    {"meaning":"a house, a home, a family, a household","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一家","answer":["いっか"]},
    {"meaning":"a species, a kind, a variety","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一種","answer":["いっしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) one object, one body, (2) what on earth?, really?, (3) generally","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一体","answer":["いったい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) on the other hand, (2) meanwhile, (3) only, simple, in turn","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一方","answer":["いっぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"dozing, nodding off","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"居眠り","answer":["いねむり"]},
    {"meaning":"command, decree, life, destiny","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"命","answer":["いのち","みこと"]},
    {"meaning":"violation (of law), transgression, infringement, breach","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"違反","answer":["いはん"]},
    {"meaning":"living room (western style)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"居間","answer":["いま"]},
    {"meaning":"since, henceforth","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"以来","answer":["いらい"]},
    {"meaning":"so to speak","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"言わば","answer":["いわば"]},
    {"meaning":"retire","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引退","answer":["いんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"quotation, citation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引用","answer":["いんよう"]},
    {"question":"鼻","answer":["はな"],"meaning":"nose"},
    {"meaning":"to receive, to get, to accept, to take","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受け取る","answer":["うけとる"]},
    {"meaning":"to move, to shift","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"動かす","answer":["うごかす"]},
    {"meaning":"cattle, cow","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"牛","answer":["うし","ぎゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to lose, to part with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"失う","answer":["うしなう"]},
    {"meaning":"to doubt, to distrust, to be suspicious of, to suspect","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"疑う","answer":["うたがう"]},
    {"question":"謝る","answer":["あやまる"],"meaning":"to apologize; to apologise"},
    {"meaning":"(1) horse, (2) promoted bishop (shogi)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"馬","answer":["うま"]},
    {"meaning":"to be sold","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売れる","answer":["うれる"]},
    {"meaning":"fortune, luck","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"運","answer":["うん"]},
    {"question":"翻訳","answer":["ほんやく"],"meaning":"translation, de-encryption; deciphering, rendering"},
    {"question":"絹","answer":["きぬ"],"meaning":"silk"},
    {"meaning":"smiling face","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"笑顔","answer":["えがお"]},
    {"meaning":"to get, to gain, to win","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"得る","answer":["える","うる"]},
    {"meaning":"speech, address","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"演説","answer":["えんぜつ"]},
    {"meaning":"honourable","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御","answer":["お","ご"]},
    {"meaning":"old age, old person, the old, the aged","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"老い","answer":["おい"]},
    {"meaning":"to overtake, to catch up (with)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追い付く","answer":["おいつく"]},
    {"meaning":"king, ruler, sovereign, monarch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"王","answer":["おう"]},
    {"meaning":"to chase, to run after","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追う","answer":["おう"]},
    {"meaning":"king","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"王様","answer":["おうさま"]},
    {"meaning":"prince","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"王子","answer":["おうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"crossing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"横断","answer":["おうだん"]},
    {"meaning":"to finish","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"終える","answer":["おえる"]},
    {"meaning":"rich family, distinguished family","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大家","answer":["おおや"]},
    {"meaning":"to occur, to happen","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"起こる","answer":["おこる"]},
    {"meaning":"to obtain, to reap, to pay, to supply, to accept","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"収める","answer":["おさめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to fear, to be afraid of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恐れる","answer":["おそれる"]},
    {"meaning":"terrible, dreadful","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恐ろしい","answer":["おそろしい"]},
    {"meaning":"mutual, reciprocal, each other","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お互い","answer":["おたがい"]},
    {"meaning":"stomach","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お腹","answer":["おなか"]},
    {"meaning":"lunch, noon","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"お昼","answer":["おひる"]},
    {"question":"看護師","answer":["かんごし"],"meaning":"(hospital) nurse; registered nurse; RN"},
    {"meaning":"memories, recollections, reminiscence","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"思い出","answer":["おもいで"]},
    {"meaning":"mainly, primarily","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"主に","answer":["おもに"]},
    {"meaning":"unintentional, spontaneous","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"思わず","answer":["おもわず"]},
    {"meaning":"swimming","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"泳ぎ","answer":["およぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"to take down, to launch, to drop","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"降ろす","answer":["おろす"]},
    {"question":"漬ける","answer":["つける"],"meaning":"to soak; to seep; to dip in, to pickle"},
    {"meaning":"meeting, assembly, party, association, club","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"会","answer":["かい"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for occurrences","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回","answer":["かい"]},
    {"meaning":"injury, harm, evil influence, damage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"害","answer":["がい"]},
    {"meaning":"member, the membership","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"会員","answer":["かいいん"]},
    {"meaning":"picture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絵画","answer":["かいが"]},
    {"meaning":"foreign, abroad, overseas","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"海外","answer":["かいがい"]},
    {"meaning":"account, finance, accountant","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"会計","answer":["かいけい"]},
    {"meaning":"settlement, solution, resolution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解決","answer":["かいけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting, assembly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"会合","answer":["かいごう"]},
    {"meaning":"diplomacy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"外交","answer":["がいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"start, commencement, beginning","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"開始","answer":["かいし"]},
    {"meaning":"painter, artist","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"画家","answer":["がか"]},
    {"meaning":"to hold or carry under or in the arms","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"抱える","answer":["かかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"chemistry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"化学","answer":["かがく"]},
    {"meaning":"official, duty, person in charge","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"係","answer":["かかり"]},
    {"meaning":"to take (e.g. time, money, etc), to hang","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"掛かる","answer":["かかる"]},
    {"meaning":"to restrict, to limit, to confine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"限る","answer":["かぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"furniture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"家具","answer":["かぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"certainty, reliability, soundness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確実","answer":["かくじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"scholar","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"学者","answer":["がくしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"study, learning","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"学習","answer":["がくしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"affirmation, confirmation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確認","answer":["かくにん"]},
    {"meaning":"scholarship, study, learning","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"学問","answer":["がくもん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be lacking","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欠ける","answer":["かける"]},
    {"meaning":"the past, bygone days, the previous","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過去","answer":["かこ"]},
    {"question":"泥棒","answer":["どろぼう"],"meaning":"thief; burglar; robber; theft"},
    {"meaning":"housework, domestic chores","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"家事","answer":["かじ"]},
    {"meaning":"singer","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"歌手","answer":["かしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"number, figure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"数","answer":["かず","すう"]},
    {"meaning":"to count","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"数える","answer":["かぞえる"]},
    {"meaning":"persons, this and that, here and there, everywhere","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"方々","answer":["かたがた","ほうぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"win, victory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勝ち","answer":["かち"]},
    {"meaning":"energy, liveliness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活気","answer":["かっき"]},
    {"meaning":"term (school)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"学期","answer":["がっき"]},
    {"meaning":"shape, form, posture, suitability","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"格好","answer":["かっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"action, activity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活動","answer":["かつどう"]},
    {"meaning":"conjugation, practical use","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活用","answer":["かつよう"]},
    {"meaning":"to be sad, to mourn for, to regret","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"悲しむ","answer":["かなしむ"]},
    {"meaning":"(not) always, (not) necessarily, (not) all, (not) entirely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"必ずしも","answer":["かならずしも"]},
    {"question":"汽車","answer":["きしゃ"],"meaning":"train (sometimes specifically a steam train)"},
    {"meaning":"to mind, to care about, to be concerned about","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"構う","answer":["かまう"]},
    {"meaning":"god","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"神","answer":["かみ"]},
    {"meaning":"(school) subject, curriculum, course","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"科目","answer":["かもく"]},
    {"question":"沸く","answer":["わく"],"meaning":"to grow hot (e.g. water); to boil, to get excited (at); to erupt (in applause, cheering, etc.); to be in a ferment; to take place energetically, to ferment, to melt (of metal)"},
    {"meaning":"thinking, thought, ideas, intention","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"考え","answer":["かんがえ"]},
    {"meaning":"sense, sensation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感覚","answer":["かんかく"]},
    {"meaning":"audience, spectator(s)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観客","answer":["かんきゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"sightseeing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観光","answer":["かんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"observation, survey","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観察","answer":["かんさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"feeling, sense, impression","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感じ","answer":["かんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"emotion(s), feeling(s), sentiment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感情","answer":["かんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to feel, to sense, to experience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感じる","answer":["かんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"admiration, Well done!","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感心","answer":["かんしん"]},
    {"meaning":"concern, interest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関心","answer":["かんしん"]},
    {"meaning":"to concern, to be related","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関する","answer":["かんする"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) complete, completion, (2) perfection, accomplishment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"完成","answer":["かんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"perfection, completeness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"完全","answer":["かんぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"being deeply moved, excitement, impression, deep emotion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感動","answer":["かんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"relation, connection, relevance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関連","answer":["かんれん"]},
    {"meaning":"member of the Diet, congress or parliament","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議員","answer":["ぎいん"]},
    {"meaning":"Diet, congress, parliament","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議会","answer":["ぎかい"]},
    {"meaning":"period, term","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"期間","answer":["きかん"]},
    {"meaning":"organ, mechanism, facility, engine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"機関","answer":["きかん"]},
    {"meaning":"climate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"気候","answer":["きこう"]},
    {"meaning":"birthplace","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生地","answer":["きじ"]},
    {"meaning":"article, news story, report, account","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記事","answer":["きじ"]},
    {"meaning":"reporter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記者","answer":["きしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"expectation, anticipation, hope","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"期待","answer":["きたい"]},
    {"meaning":"returning home","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"帰宅","answer":["きたく"]},
    {"meaning":"chairman","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議長","answer":["ぎちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to notice, to recognize, to become aware of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"気付く","answer":["きづく"]},
    {"meaning":"entry, filling in of forms","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記入","answer":["きにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"commemoration, memory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記念","answer":["きねん"]},
    {"meaning":"function, faculty","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"機能","answer":["きのう"]},
    {"meaning":"contribution, donation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寄付","answer":["きふ"]},
    {"meaning":"settlement, conclusion, regulation, rule","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決まり","answer":["きまり"]},
    {"meaning":"-like, -looking, -looked","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"気味","answer":["きみ"]},
    {"meaning":"question, problem, doubt, guess","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"疑問","answer":["ぎもん"]},
    {"meaning":"globe, sphere, ball","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"球","answer":["きゅう","たま"]},
    {"meaning":"absorption, suction, attraction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"吸収","answer":["きゅうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"rapid (e.g. progress)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"急速","answer":["きゅうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"急に","answer":["きゅうに"]},
    {"meaning":"salary, wages","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"給料","answer":["きゅうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"text book","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"教科書","answer":["きょうかしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"supply, provision","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"供給","answer":["きょうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"teacher (classroom)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"教師","answer":["きょうし"]},
    {"meaning":"emphasis, stress, stressed point","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"強調","answer":["きょうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"commonness, community","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共通","answer":["きょうつう"]},
    {"meaning":"cooperation, association, collaboration, joint","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共同","answer":["きょうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"be afraid, dread, dismay, terror","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恐怖","answer":["きょうふ"]},
    {"meaning":"herculean strength, mountain carrier-guide","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"強力","answer":["きょうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"court lady, lady in waiting","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"局","answer":["きょく","つぼね"]},
    {"meaning":"cloth, piece, cut, chop","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"切れ","answer":["きれ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to cut well, to be sharp, (2) to break (off)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"切れる","answer":["きれる"]},
    {"meaning":"argument, discussion, dispute","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議論","answer":["ぎろん"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) silver, silver coin, silver paint","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"銀","answer":["ぎん","しろがね"]},
    {"meaning":"present day","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"近代","answer":["きんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"(by) chance, unexpectedly, suddenly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"偶然","answer":["ぐうぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"concrete, tangible, material","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"具体","answer":["ぐたい"]},
    {"meaning":"pain, agony","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦痛","answer":["くつう"]},
    {"meaning":"class, group, team, set","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組","answer":["くみ"]},
    {"meaning":"association, union","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組合","answer":["くみあい"]},
    {"meaning":"to put together","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組む","answer":["くむ"]},
    {"meaning":"living, livelihood, subsistence, circumstances","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暮らし","answer":["くらし"]},
    {"meaning":"to live, to get along","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暮らす","answer":["くらす"]},
    {"meaning":"painful, difficult","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦しい","answer":["くるしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to suffer, to groan, to be worried","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦しむ","answer":["くるしむ"]},
    {"meaning":"year end, sunset, nightfall, end","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暮れ","answer":["くれ"]},
    {"meaning":"troubles, hardships","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦労","answer":["くろう"]},
    {"meaning":"to append, to sum up, to add (up)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加える","answer":["くわえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to join in, to accede to, to increase, to gain in (influence)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加わる","answer":["くわわる"]},
    {"question":"沸かす","answer":["わかす"],"meaning":"to boil; to heat, to excite, to melt (metal)"},
    {"meaning":"to plan","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"計画","answer":["けいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"condition, state, business (condition)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"景気","answer":["けいき"]},
    {"meaning":"experience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経験","answer":["けいけん"]},
    {"meaning":"warning, advice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"警告","answer":["けいこく"]},
    {"meaning":"go by the way, via","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経由","answer":["けいゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"determination, resolution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決心","answer":["けっしん"]},
    {"meaning":"absence, non-attendance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欠席","answer":["けっせき"]},
    {"meaning":"decision, determination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決定","answer":["けってい"]},
    {"meaning":"faults, defect, weakness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欠点","answer":["けってん"]},
    {"meaning":"smoke, fumes","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"煙","answer":["けむり","けむ"]},
    {"meaning":"opinion, point of view","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見解","answer":["けんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"limit, bound","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"限界","answer":["げんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"cash, ready money, mercenary, self-interested","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現金","answer":["げんきん"]},
    {"meaning":"language","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"言語","answer":["げんご"]},
    {"meaning":"present, up to now, nowadays, modern times, current","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現在","answer":["げんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"reality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現実","answer":["げんじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"present condition, existing state, status quo","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現状","answer":["げんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"nowadays, modern times, present-day","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現代","answer":["げんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"be found, aim, estimate, guess, approx","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見当","answer":["けんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"actual spot, scene, scene of the crime","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現場","answer":["げんば","げんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"right, privilege","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"権利","answer":["けんり"]},
    {"meaning":"good luck, fortune","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"幸運","answer":["こううん"]},
    {"meaning":"success, passing (e.g. exam), eligibility","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合格","answer":["ごうかく"]},
    {"meaning":"scene, spectacle","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"光景","answer":["こうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"sum total, total amount","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合計","answer":["ごうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"advertisement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"広告","answer":["こうこく"]},
    {"meaning":"company, friendship, association, society, acquaintance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交際","answer":["こうさい"]},
    {"meaning":"the latter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"後者","answer":["こうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"factory","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"工場","answer":["こうじょう","こうば"]},
    {"meaning":"organization, composition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"構成","answer":["こうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"high speed, high gear","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"高速","answer":["こうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"action, conduct, behaviour, mobilization","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"行動","answer":["こうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"robbery, burglary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"強盗","answer":["ごうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"happiness, blessedness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"幸福","answer":["こうふく"]},
    {"meaning":"fairness, impartial, justice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公平","answer":["こうへい"]},
    {"meaning":"to exceed, to cross over, to cross","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"越える","answer":["こえる"]},
    {"meaning":"misunderstanding","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"誤解","answer":["ごかい"]},
    {"meaning":"breath, respiration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"呼吸","answer":["こきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"national, people, citizen","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"国民","answer":["こくみん"]},
    {"meaning":"to go over (e.g. with audience)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"越す","answer":["こす"]},
    {"meaning":"state, country, nation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"国家","answer":["こっか"]},
    {"meaning":"National Diet, parliament, congress","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"国会","answer":["こっかい"]},
    {"meaning":"thing, matter, fact, circumstances","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"事","answer":["こと"]},
    {"meaning":"to refuse, to decline, to dismiss","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"断る","answer":["ことわる"]},
    {"meaning":"liking, taste, choice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好み","answer":["このみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to like, to prefer","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好む","answer":["このむ"]},
    {"meaning":"hut, cabin, shed, (animal) pen","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"小屋","answer":["こや"]},
    {"meaning":"to kill","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"殺す","answer":["ころす"]},
    {"meaning":"to fall down, to fall over","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"転ぶ","answer":["ころぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"now, this time, lately","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"今回","answer":["こんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"difficulty, distress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"困難","answer":["こんなん"]},
    {"meaning":"engagement, betrothal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"婚約","answer":["こんやく"]},
    {"meaning":"difference, variation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差","answer":["さ"]},
    {"meaning":"on the occasion of, circumstances","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"際","answer":["さい","きわ"]},
    {"meaning":"highest, supreme, the most","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最高","answer":["さいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"property, fortune, assets","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"財産","answer":["ざいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"last, final, closing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最終","answer":["さいしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"in the middle of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最中","answer":["さいちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"talent, ability","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"才能","answer":["さいのう"]},
    {"meaning":"happiness, blessedness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"幸い","answer":["さいわい"]},
    {"meaning":"work, operation, manufacturing, fatigue duty","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作業","answer":["さぎょう"]},
    {"question":"拝見","answer":["はいけん"],"meaning":"seeing; look at"},
    {"meaning":"work, opus, performance, production","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作品","answer":["さくひん"]},
    {"meaning":"produce (e.g. agricultural), crops","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作物","answer":["さくもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"alcohol, sake","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"酒","answer":["さけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to support, sustain, prop up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支える","answer":["ささえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to point, to put up umbrella, to play","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"指す","answer":["さす"]},
    {"meaning":"seat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"座席","answer":["ざせき"]},
    {"meaning":"author, writer, novelist, artist","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作家","answer":["さっか"]},
    {"meaning":"composition, setting (of music)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"作曲","answer":["さっきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"discrimination, distinction, differentiation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差別","answer":["さべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"manners, etiquette, propriety","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"作法","answer":["さほう"]},
    {"meaning":"varied, various","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"様々","answer":["さまざま"]},
    {"meaning":"to awaken","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"覚ます","answer":["さます"]},
    {"meaning":"to wake, to wake up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"覚める","answer":["さめる"]},
    {"meaning":"furthermore, again, after all, more and more, moreover","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"更に","answer":["さらに"]},
    {"meaning":"to leave, to go away","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"去る","answer":["さる"]},
    {"meaning":"participation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"参加","answer":["さんか"]},
    {"meaning":"reference, consultation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"参考","answer":["さんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"happiness, good fortune, luck, blessing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"幸せ","answer":["しあわせ"]},
    {"question":"寂しい","answer":["さびしい","さみしい"],"meaning":"lonely; lonesome; solitary; desolate"},
    {"meaning":"immediately, readily, directly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直に","answer":["じかに","じきに"]},
    {"meaning":"equation, formula, ceremony","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"式","answer":["しき"]},
    {"question":"堅い","answer":["かたい"],"meaning":"hard; solid; tough, stiff; tight; wooden; unpolished (e.g. writing), strong; firm (not viscous or easily moved), safe; steady; honest; steadfast, obstinate; stubborn, bookish; formal; stuffy"},
    {"meaning":"time, season, period","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時期","answer":["じき"]},
    {"meaning":"payment, allowance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支給","answer":["しきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"event, affair, incident","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"事件","answer":["じけん"]},
    {"meaning":"instant, time, moment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時刻","answer":["じこく"]},
    {"meaning":"suicide","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自殺","answer":["じさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"fact, truth, reality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"事実","answer":["じじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"expenditure, expenses","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支出","answer":["ししゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"circumstances, consideration, conditions, situation, reasons","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"事情","answer":["じじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"nature, spontaneous","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自然","answer":["しぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"thought, idea","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"思想","answer":["しそう"]},
    {"meaning":"preparation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支度","answer":["したく"]},
    {"meaning":"intimate, close (e.g. friend)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"親しい","answer":["したしい"]},
    {"meaning":"quality, nature (of person)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"質","answer":["しつ","しち","たち"]},
    {"meaning":"unemployment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"失業","answer":["しつぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"experiment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実験","answer":["じっけん"]},
    {"meaning":"implementation, materialization, realization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実現","answer":["じつげん"]},
    {"meaning":"practice, performance, execution (e.g. program), realization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実行","answer":["じっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"practical, actual condition, status quo","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実際","answer":["じっさい"]},
    {"meaning":"indeed, truly, surely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実に","answer":["じつに"]},
    {"meaning":"as a matter of fact, by the way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実は","answer":["じつは"]},
    {"meaning":"disappointment, despair","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"失望","answer":["しつぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"branch store (office)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支店","answer":["してん"]},
    {"meaning":"automatic, self-motion","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"自動","answer":["じどう"]},
    {"meaning":"thing, article, goods, dignity, article (goods), counter for meal courses","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"品","answer":["しな","ひん"]},
    {"meaning":"rule, control, direction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支配","answer":["しはい"]},
    {"meaning":"payment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支払","answer":["しはらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to pay","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支払う","answer":["しはらう"]},
    {"meaning":"death, mortality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"死亡","answer":["しぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"funds, capital","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"資本","answer":["しほん"]},
    {"meaning":"sisters","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"姉妹","answer":["しまい"]},
    {"meaning":"business, office work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"事務","answer":["じむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to denote, to show, to point out, to indicate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"示す","answer":["しめす"]},
    {"meaning":"debt, loan, liabilities","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"借金","answer":["しゃっきん"]},
    {"meaning":"week","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"週","answer":["しゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"week, weekly","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"週間","answer":["しゅうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"serious, important, grave, weighty","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"重大","answer":["じゅうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"resident, housing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"住宅","answer":["じゅうたく"]},
    {"meaning":"concentration, focusing the mind","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"集中","answer":["しゅうちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"income, receipts, revenue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"収入","answer":["しゅうにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"citizens, inhabitants, residents, population","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"住民","answer":["じゅうみん"]},
    {"meaning":"important, momentous, essential, principal, major","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"重要","answer":["じゅうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"surgical operation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手術","answer":["しゅじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"Prime Minister","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"首相","answer":["しゅしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"means, way, measure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手段","answer":["しゅだん"]},
    {"meaning":"attendance, presence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出席","answer":["しゅっせき"]},
    {"question":"億","answer":["おく"],"meaning":"10^8; 100,000,000; hundred million"},
    {"meaning":"capital city","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"首都","answer":["しゅと"]},
    {"meaning":"housewife, mistress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"主婦","answer":["しゅふ"]},
    {"meaning":"chief, main, principal, major","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"主要","answer":["しゅよう"]},
    {"meaning":"variety, kind, type","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"種類","answer":["しゅるい"]},
    {"meaning":"use, application, employment, utilization","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"使用","answer":["しよう"]},
    {"meaning":"passenger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗客","answer":["じょうきゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"proceeding to the capital (Tokyo)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"上京","answer":["じょうきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"noon, mid-day","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"正午","answer":["しょうご"]},
    {"meaning":"honesty, integrity, frankness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正直","answer":["しょうじき"]},
    {"meaning":"common sense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"常識","answer":["じょうしき"]},
    {"meaning":"daughter, young lady, virgin, maiden, little girl","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"少女","answer":["しょうじょ","おとめ"]},
    {"meaning":"just a minute, small quantity","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"少々","answer":["しょうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"invitation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"招待","answer":["しょうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"improvement, advance, progress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"上達","answer":["じょうたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"superiority, first class, very good","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"上等","answer":["じょうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"trader, shopkeeper, merchant","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商人","answer":["しょうにん","あきうど","あきんど","あきゅうど","あきびと"]},
    {"meaning":"boys, juveniles","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"少年","answer":["しょうねん"]},
    {"meaning":"trade, business, commerce, transaction, occupation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商売","answer":["しょうばい"]},
    {"meaning":"consumption, expenditure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"消費","answer":["しょうひ"]},
    {"meaning":"commodity, article of commerce, goods, stock, merchandise","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商品","answer":["しょうひん"]},
    {"meaning":"information, (military) intelligence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"情報","answer":["じょうほう"]},
    {"meaning":"queen","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"女王","answer":["じょおう"]},
    {"meaning":"employment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"職","answer":["しょく"]},
    {"meaning":"occupation, business","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"職業","answer":["しょくぎょう"]},
    {"question":"一生懸命","answer":["いっしょうけんめい"],"meaning":"very hard; with utmost effort; with all one's might; for dear life"},
    {"meaning":"commodity, foodstuff","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"食品","answer":["しょくひん"]},
    {"meaning":"food, foodstuff","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"食物","answer":["しょくもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"appetite (for food)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"食欲","answer":["しょくよく"]},
    {"meaning":"food","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"食料","answer":["しょくりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"helper, helpmeet, assistant, tutor","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"助手","answer":["じょしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"books","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"書物","answer":["しょもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"actress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"女優","answer":["じょゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"processing, dealing with, treatment, disposition, disposal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"処理","answer":["しょり"]},
    {"meaning":"documents, official papers","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"書類","answer":["しょるい"]},
    {"meaning":"notice","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"知らせ","answer":["しらせ"]},
    {"meaning":"going on to university","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進学","answer":["しんがく"]},
    {"meaning":"nerve, sensitivity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"神経","answer":["しんけい"]},
    {"meaning":"traffic lights, signal, semaphore","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信号","answer":["しんごう"]},
    {"meaning":"artificial, manmade, human work, human skill, artificiality","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"人工","answer":["じんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"serious","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"深刻","answer":["しんこく"]},
    {"meaning":"race (of people)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人種","answer":["じんしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"to believe, to place trust in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信じる","answer":["しんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"worry, concern, anxiety, care","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"心配","answer":["しんぱい"]},
    {"meaning":"character, personality, person, man, personage, talented man","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"人物","answer":["じんぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"progress, development","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進歩","answer":["しんぽ"]},
    {"meaning":"close friend, buddy","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"親友","answer":["しんゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"confidence, dependence, credit, faith","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信用","answer":["しんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"reliance, trust, confidence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信頼","answer":["しんらい"]},
    {"meaning":"mentality","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"心理","answer":["しんり"]},
    {"meaning":"mankind, humanity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人類","answer":["じんるい"]},
    {"meaning":"figure (e.g. Fig 1), drawing, picture, illustration","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"図","answer":["ず"]},
    {"meaning":"numeral, figure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"数字","answer":["すうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"the end of, powder","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"末","answer":["すえ","まつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to open, to become empty","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"空く","answer":["あく","すく"]},
    {"meaning":"to surpass, to outstrip, to excel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"優れる","answer":["すぐれる"]},
    {"meaning":"anything of, not one bit","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"少しも","answer":["すこしも"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass, to spend, to go through, to tide over","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過ごす","answer":["すごす"]},
    {"meaning":"to advance, to promote, to hasten","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進める","answer":["すすめる"]},
    {"meaning":"headache","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"頭痛","answer":["ずつう"]},
    {"meaning":"all, the whole, entirely, in general, wholly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全て","answer":["すべて"]},
    {"meaning":"to be finished","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"済ませる","answer":["すませる"]},
    {"meaning":"(logical) true, regular","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"正","answer":["せい"]},
    {"meaning":"sex, gender","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"性","answer":["せい","さが"]},
    {"meaning":"character, personality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"性格","answer":["せいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"accurate, punctuality, exactness, authenticity, veracity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正確","answer":["せいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"restriction, restraint, limitation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制限","answer":["せいげん"]},
    {"meaning":"production, manufacture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"生産","answer":["せいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"due form, official, formality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正式","answer":["せいしき"]},
    {"meaning":"mind, soul, heart, spirit, intention","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"精神","answer":["せいしん"]},
    {"meaning":"adult","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"成人","answer":["せいじん"]},
    {"meaning":"growth, grow to adulthood","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"成長","answer":["せいちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"system, institution, organization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制度","answer":["せいど"]},
    {"meaning":"youth, young man","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"青年","answer":["せいねん"]},
    {"meaning":"raw food","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生物","answer":["せいぶつ","なまもの"]},
    {"meaning":"life, existence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"生命","answer":["せいめい"]},
    {"meaning":"duty, responsibility","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"責任","answer":["せきにん"]},
    {"meaning":"world, society","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"世間","answer":["せけん"]},
    {"meaning":"theory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"説","answer":["せつ"]},
    {"meaning":"absolute, unconditional, absoluteness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絶対","answer":["ぜったい"]},
    {"meaning":"to condemn, to blame, to criticize","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"責める","answer":["せめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to look after","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"世話","answer":["せわ"]},
    {"question":"お嬢さん","answer":["おじょうさん"],"meaning":"daughter, young lady"},
    {"meaning":"all members (unanimity), all hands, the whole crew","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全員","answer":["ぜんいん"]},
    {"meaning":"country-wide, nation-wide, whole country, national","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全国","answer":["ぜんこく"]},
    {"meaning":"the former","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"前者","answer":["ぜんしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) player (in game), (2) team","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"選手","answer":["せんしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"advance, drive, progress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"前進","answer":["ぜんしん"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) wholly, entirely, completely, (2) not at all (with neg. verb)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全然","answer":["ぜんぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"whole, entirety, whatever (is the matter)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全体","answer":["ぜんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"increase, addition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増加","answer":["ぞうか"]},
    {"meaning":"succession, inheritance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相続","answer":["そうぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"consultation, discussion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相談","answer":["そうだん"]},
    {"meaning":"suitable, fair, tolerable, proper","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相当","answer":["そうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"speed, velocity, rate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"速度","answer":["そくど"]},
    {"meaning":"to pour (into), to irrigate, to pay, to fill, to feed (e.g. a fire)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"注ぐ","answer":["そそぐ","つぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to raise (child), to be brought up, to grow (up)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"育つ","answer":["そだつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to furnish, to provide for, to equip, to install","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"備える","answer":["そなえる"]},
    {"meaning":"side, edge, third person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"側","answer":["そば","かわ","がわ"]},
    {"meaning":"existence, being","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"存在","answer":["そんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"rice field","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"田","answer":["た"]},
    {"meaning":"other (esp. places and things)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"他","answer":["た","ほか"]},
    {"meaning":"pair, couple, set","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対","answer":["たい","つい"]},
    {"meaning":"stand, rack, table, support","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"台","answer":["だい","うてな"]},
    {"meaning":"title, subject, theme, topic","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"題","answer":["だい"]},
    {"meaning":"physical education, gymnastics, athletics","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"体育","answer":["たいいく"]},
    {"meaning":"convention, tournament, mass meeting, rally","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大会","answer":["たいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"price, payment, cost, charge","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"代金","answer":["だいきん"]},
    {"meaning":"ambassador","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大使","answer":["たいし"]},
    {"meaning":"to face, to confront, to oppose","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対する","answer":["たいする"]},
    {"meaning":"great war, great battle","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"大戦","answer":["たいせん"]},
    {"meaning":"representative, representation, delegation, type, example, model","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"代表","answer":["だいひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"awful, dreadful, terrible, very","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"大変","answer":["たいへん"]},
    {"meaning":"sun, solar","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"太陽","answer":["たいよう"]},
    {"meaning":"flatness, level, smooth, calm, plain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平ら","answer":["たいら"]},
    {"meaning":"representation, agency, proxy, deputy, agent","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"代理","answer":["だいり"]},
    {"meaning":"to throw down, to beat, to bring down, to blow down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"倒す","answer":["たおす"]},
    {"meaning":"mutual, reciprocal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"互い","answer":["たがい"]},
    {"question":"鉛筆","answer":["えんぴつ"],"meaning":"pencil"},
    {"meaning":"to ascertain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確かめる","answer":["たしかめる"]},
    {"meaning":"more or less, somewhat, a little, some","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"多少","answer":["たしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to help, to save, to rescue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"助ける","answer":["たすける"]},
    {"meaning":"battle, fight, struggle, conflict","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戦い","answer":["たたかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to fight, to battle, to combat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戦う","answer":["たたかう"]},
    {"meaning":"at once, immediately, directly, in person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直ちに","answer":["ただちに"]},
    {"meaning":"to stand up","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"立ち上がる","answer":["たちあがる"]},
    {"meaning":"standpoint, position, situation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"立場","answer":["たちば"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass, to lapse","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経つ","answer":["たつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to reach, to get to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"達する","answer":["たっする"]},
    {"meaning":"another person, unrelated person, outsider, stranger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"他人","answer":["たにん","あだびと"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) seed, (2) material, (3) cause, source","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"種","answer":["たね","しゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"handbreadth, bundle","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"束","answer":["たば","つか"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for occurrences","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"度","answer":["たび","ど"]},
    {"meaning":"travel, trip, journey","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"旅","answer":["たび"]},
    {"meaning":"trial, test","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"試し","answer":["ためし"]},
    {"meaning":"to attempt, to test","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"試す","answer":["ためす"]},
    {"meaning":"news, tidings, information, correspondence, letter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"便り","answer":["たより"]},
    {"meaning":"to rely on, to have recourse to, to depend on","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"頼る","answer":["たよる"]},
    {"meaning":"step, stair, flight of steps, grade, rank, level","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"段","answer":["だん"]},
    {"meaning":"unit, denomination, credit (in school)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単位","answer":["たんい"]},
    {"meaning":"word, vocabulary, (usually) single-character word","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単語","answer":["たんご"]},
    {"meaning":"mere, simple, sheer","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単なる","answer":["たんなる"]},
    {"meaning":"simply, merely, only, solely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単に","answer":["たんに"]},
    {"meaning":"earth","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地","answer":["ち"]},
    {"meaning":"(social) position, status","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"地位","answer":["ちい"]},
    {"meaning":"basement, underground","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地下","answer":["ちか"]},
    {"meaning":"difference, discrepancy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"違い","answer":["ちがい","たがい"]},
    {"meaning":"(phrase) sure, no mistaking it, for certain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"違いない","answer":["ちがいない"]},
    {"meaning":"the earth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"地球","answer":["ちきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"lateness, late coming","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遅刻","answer":["ちこく"]},
    {"meaning":"prefectural governor","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"知事","answer":["ちじ"]},
    {"meaning":"knowledge, information","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"知識","answer":["ちしき"]},
    {"meaning":"father","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"父親","answer":["ちちおや"]},
    {"meaning":"intelligence, brains","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"知能","answer":["ちのう"]},
    {"meaning":"area, locality, district, region, the coast","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地方","answer":["ちほう"]},
    {"meaning":"tea","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"茶","answer":["ちゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"annotation, explanatory note","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"注","answer":["ちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) used, second-hand, old","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"中古","answer":["ちゅうこ"]},
    {"meaning":"suspension, stoppage, discontinuance, interruption","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"中止","answer":["ちゅうし"]},
    {"meaning":"lunch, midday meal","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"昼食","answer":["ちゅうしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"center, core, heart, pivot, emphasis, balance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"中心","answer":["ちゅうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"notice, attention, observation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"注目","answer":["ちゅうもく"]},
    {"meaning":"order, request","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"注文","answer":["ちゅうもん"]},
    {"meaning":"long time period","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"長期","answer":["ちょうき"]},
    {"meaning":"tune, tone, key","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"調子","answer":["ちょうし"]},
    {"meaning":"top, summit, peak","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"頂上","answer":["ちょうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"passage through, passing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通過","answer":["つうか"]},
    {"meaning":"commuting to school","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通学","answer":["つうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"passage, passing","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通行","answer":["つうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"to run to, to lead to, to communicate, to understand","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通じる","answer":["つうじる"]},
    {"meaning":"correspondence, communication, news, signal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通信","answer":["つうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be caught, to be arrested","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"捕まる","answer":["つかまる"]},
    {"meaning":"tiredness, fatigue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"疲れ","answer":["つかれ"]},
    {"meaning":"association, socializing, fellowship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付き合い","answer":["つきあい"]},
    {"meaning":"in succession, one by one","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"次々","answer":["つぎつぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"to attach, to join, to add, to append","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付ける","answer":["つける"]},
    {"meaning":"sequel, continuation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"続き","answer":["つづき"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) service, duty, business, responsibility, task, (2) Buddhist religious services","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勤め","answer":["つとめ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) service, duty, (2) Buddhist religious services","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"務め","answer":["つとめ"]},
    {"meaning":"always, constantly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"常に","answer":["つねに"]},
    {"meaning":"crime, fault, indiscretion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"罪","answer":["つみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to pile up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"積もる","answer":["つもる"]},
    {"meaning":"companion, company","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連れ","answer":["つれ"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting, rendezvous, encounter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出会い","answer":["であい"]},
    {"meaning":"to meet by chance, to come across, to happen to encounter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出会う","answer":["であう"]},
    {"meaning":"fixed term","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定期","answer":["ていき"]},
    {"meaning":"degree, amount, grade, standard, of the order of (following a number)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"程度","answer":["ていど"]},
    {"meaning":"incident, affair, happening, event","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出来事","answer":["できごと"]},
    {"meaning":"to fit, to suit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適する","answer":["てきする"]},
    {"meaning":"pertinent, appropriate, adequate, relevance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適切","answer":["てきせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"moderate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適度","answer":["てきど"]},
    {"meaning":"applying","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適用","answer":["てきよう"]},
    {"meaning":"sleight of hand, conjuring trick, magic, juggling","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手品","answer":["てじな"]},
    {"meaning":"help, helper, assistant","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手伝い","answer":["てつだい"]},
    {"meaning":"time, labour","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手間","answer":["てま"]},
    {"meaning":"weather","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"天候","answer":["てんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"nature, spontaneity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"天然","answer":["てんねん"]},
    {"meaning":"question, query","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"問い","answer":["とい"]},
    {"meaning":"identity, sameness, similarity","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"同一","answer":["どういつ"]},
    {"meaning":"at that time, in those days","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当時","answer":["とうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"simultaneous(ly), concurrent, same time, synchronous","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"同時","answer":["どうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"arrival","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"到着","answer":["とうちゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"identical, equal to, same (kind), like","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"同様","answer":["どうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"road, highway","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"道路","answer":["どうろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to let pass, to overlook, to continue","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通す","answer":["とおす"]},
    {"meaning":"in accordance with ~, following ~, ~ Street, ~ Avenue","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通り","answer":["とおり"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass, to pass through","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通り過ぎる","answer":["とおりすぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"city","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"都会","answer":["とかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to unfasten","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解く","answer":["とく","ほどく"]},
    {"meaning":"pride, triumph, prosperity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"得意","answer":["とくい"]},
    {"meaning":"to come untied, to come apart","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解ける","answer":["とける","ほどける"]},
    {"meaning":"mountain-climbing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"登山","answer":["とざん"]},
    {"meaning":"town, city, municipal, urban","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"都市","answer":["とし"]},
    {"meaning":"books","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"図書","answer":["としょ"]},
    {"meaning":"old people, the aged","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"年寄","answer":["としより"]},
    {"meaning":"to close (e.g. book, eyes), to shut","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"閉じる","answer":["とじる"]},
    {"meaning":"plot of land, lot, soil","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"土地","answer":["とち"]},
    {"meaning":"abruptly, suddenly, unexpectedly, all at once","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突然","answer":["とつぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"to skip over, to omit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"飛ばす","answer":["とばす"]},
    {"meaning":"to jump out, to rush out, to fly out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"飛び出す","answer":["とびだす"]},
    {"meaning":"to fasten, to turn off, to detain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留める","answer":["とめる","とどめる"]},
    {"meaning":"sharing with, participate in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共に","answer":["ともに"]},
    {"meaning":"to take up, to pick up, to disqualify, to confiscate, to deprive","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り上げる","answer":["とりあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"great effort, exertion, endeavour, effort","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"努力","answer":["どりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to come off, to be taken off, to be removed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取れる","answer":["とれる"]},
    {"meaning":"subject, contents, matter, substance, detail, import","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"内容","answer":["ないよう"]},
    {"meaning":"to drain, to float, to shed (blood, tears), to cruise (e.g. taxi)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流す","answer":["ながす"]},
    {"meaning":"stream, current","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流れ","answer":["ながれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to stream, to flow, to run (ink), to be washed away","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流れる","answer":["ながれる"]},
    {"meaning":"et cetera, etc., and the like","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"等","answer":["など","とう"]},
    {"meaning":"to suit, to match, to become, to be like","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"似合う","answer":["にあう"]},
    {"meaning":"poor (at), weak (in), dislike (of)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦手","answer":["にがて"]},
    {"meaning":"ordinary, regular, everyday, usual","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日常","answer":["にちじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"sunlight","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日光","answer":["にっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"to hospitalise","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"入院","answer":["にゅういん"]},
    {"meaning":"entrance, admission, entering","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"入場","answer":["にゅうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to extract, to omit, to surpass, to draw out, to unplug","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"抜く","answer":["ぬく"]},
    {"meaning":"to come out, to fall out, to be omitted","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"抜ける","answer":["ぬける"]},
    {"meaning":"value, price, cost","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"値","answer":["ね","あたい"]},
    {"meaning":"desire, wish, request","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"願い","answer":["ねがい"]},
    {"meaning":"to desire, to wish, to request","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"願う","answer":["ねがう"]},
    {"meaning":"price, cost","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"値段","answer":["ねだん"]},
    {"meaning":"zeal, enthusiasm","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"熱心","answer":["ねっしん"]},
    {"meaning":"nuts!, enthusiasm, zeal, mania","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"熱中","answer":["ねっちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"age, era, period, date","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"年代","answer":["ねんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"field","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"野","answer":["の","や"]},
    {"meaning":"being skilled in, nicely, properly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"能","answer":["のう"]},
    {"meaning":"ability, faculty","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"能力","answer":["のうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to leave (behind, over), to bequeath, to save, to reserve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残す","answer":["のこす"]},
    {"meaning":"remnant, residue, remaining, left-over","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残り","answer":["のこり"]},
    {"meaning":"to place on (something), to take on board, to give a ride","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗せる","answer":["のせる"]},
    {"meaning":"to remove, to exclude, to except","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"除く","answer":["のぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"wish, desire, (a) hope","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"望み","answer":["のぞみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to desire, to wish for, to see, to command (a view of)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"望む","answer":["のぞむ"]},
    {"meaning":"place, field (physics)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"場","answer":["ば"]},
    {"meaning":"delivery, distribution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"配達","answer":["はいたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to measure, to weigh, to survey","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"計る","answer":["はかる"]},
    {"meaning":"(personal) bankruptcy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"破産","answer":["はさん"]},
    {"meaning":"origin, beginning","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"始まり","answer":["はじまり"]},
    {"meaning":"work, labor","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"働き","answer":["はたらき"]},
    {"meaning":"discovery, detection, finding","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発見","answer":["はっけん"]},
    {"meaning":"issue (publications)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発行","answer":["はっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"departure of a vehicle","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発車","answer":["はっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"development, growth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"発達","answer":["はったつ"]},
    {"meaning":"announcement, publication","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"発表","answer":["はっぴょう"]},
    {"meaning":"invention","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発明","answer":["はつめい"]},
    {"meaning":"to discuss, to talk together","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"話し合う","answer":["はなしあう"]},
    {"meaning":"to separate, to set free","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放す","answer":["はなす"]},
    {"meaning":"mother","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"母親","answer":["ははおや"]},
    {"meaning":"scene, setting (e.g. of novel)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"場面","answer":["ばめん"]},
    {"meaning":"abdomen, belly, stomach","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"腹","answer":["はら"]},
    {"meaning":"field, plain, prairie, tundra, moor, wilderness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原","answer":["はら"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"番","answer":["ばん"]},
    {"meaning":"crime","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"犯罪","answer":["はんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"judgement, decision","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"判断","answer":["はんだん"]},
    {"meaning":"offender, criminal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"犯人","answer":["はんにん"]},
    {"meaning":"aviation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"飛行","answer":["ひこう"]},
    {"meaning":"emergency, extraordinary, unusual","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"非常","answer":["ひじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"beautiful person (woman)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"美人","answer":["びじん"]},
    {"meaning":"date, dating","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日付","answer":["ひづけ"]},
    {"meaning":"inevitable death, desperation, frantic, inevitable result","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"必死","answer":["ひっし"]},
    {"meaning":"negation, denial, repudiation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"否定","answer":["ひてい"]},
    {"meaning":"single word","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一言","answer":["ひとこと"]},
    {"meaning":"crowd of people","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人込み","answer":["ひとごみ"]},
    {"meaning":"equal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"等しい","answer":["ひとしい"]},
    {"meaning":"cost, expense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"費用","answer":["ひよう"]},
    {"meaning":"table (e.g. Tab 1), chart, list","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表","answer":["ひょう","おもて"]},
    {"meaning":"expression, presentation, representation (math)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表現","answer":["ひょうげん"]},
    {"meaning":"facial expression","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表情","answer":["ひょうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"equality (a), impartiality, evenness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平等","answer":["びょうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"surface, outside, face, appearance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表面","answer":["ひょうめん"]},
    {"meaning":"to spread (out), to extend, to stretch, to reach to, to get around","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"広がる","answer":["ひろがる"]},
    {"meaning":"way, means","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"便","answer":["びん","べん"]},
    {"meaning":"un, non, negative prefix","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不","answer":["ふ"]},
    {"meaning":"anxiety, uneasiness, insecurity, suspense","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不安","answer":["ふあん"]},
    {"meaning":"scenery","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"風景","answer":["ふうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"married couple, husband and wife","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夫婦","answer":["ふうふ"]},
    {"meaning":"unhappiness, sorrow, misfortune, disaster, accident, death","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不幸","answer":["ふこう"]},
    {"meaning":"mystery, curiosity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不思議","answer":["ふしぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"discomfort, disability, inconvenience, destitution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不自由","answer":["ふじゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"wife, Mrs, madam","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夫人","answer":["ふじん"]},
    {"meaning":"woman, female","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"婦人","answer":["ふじん"]},
    {"meaning":"injustice, unfairness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不正","answer":["ふせい"]},
    {"meaning":"insufficiency, shortage, deficiency, lack, dearth","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不足","answer":["ふそく"]},
    {"meaning":"stage (theatre)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"舞台","answer":["ぶたい"]},
    {"question":"脱ぐ","answer":["ぬぐ"],"meaning":"to take off (clothes, shoes, etc.); to undress"},
    {"meaning":"material, substance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物質","answer":["ぶっしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"physics","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物理","answer":["ぶつり"]},
    {"question":"玄関","answer":["げんかん"],"meaning":"entranceway; entry hall; vestibule; foyer; entryway; mud room"},
    {"meaning":"complaint, discontent, dissatisfaction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不平","answer":["ふへい"]},
    {"meaning":"dissatisfaction, displeasure, discontent, complaints, unhappiness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不満","answer":["ふまん"]},
    {"meaning":"disadvantage, handicap, unfavorable, drawback","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不利","answer":["ふり"]},
    {"meaning":"sentence","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"文","answer":["ぶん","ふみ"]},
    {"meaning":"civilization, culture","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"文明","answer":["ぶんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"peace, harmony","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平和","answer":["へいわ"]},
    {"meaning":"(not) particularly, nothing","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"別に","answer":["べつに"]},
    {"meaning":"goblin, ghost, apparition, bugbear","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"変化","answer":["へんか"]},
    {"question":"狭い","answer":["せまい"],"meaning":"narrow; confined; small"},
    {"meaning":"change, modification, alteration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"変更","answer":["へんこう"]},
    {"question":"灰皿","answer":["はいざら"],"meaning":"ashtray"},
    {"meaning":"Act (law: the X Act)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"法","answer":["ほう"]},
    {"meaning":"direction, course, way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"方向","answer":["ほうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"report, information","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"報告","answer":["ほうこく"]},
    {"meaning":"broadcast, broadcasting","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放送","answer":["ほうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"method, manner, way, means, technique","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"方法","answer":["ほうほう"]},
    {"meaning":"call, visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"訪問","answer":["ほうもん"]},
    {"meaning":"degree, extent, bounds, limit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"程","answer":["ほど"]},
    {"meaning":"footpath, walkway, sidewalk","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"歩道","answer":["ほどう"]},
    {"meaning":"truth, reality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"本当","answer":["ほんと","ほんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"genuine article","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"本物","answer":["ほんもの"]},
    {"meaning":"lost (stray) child","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"迷子","answer":["まいご"]},
    {"meaning":"to entrust to another, to leave to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"任せる","answer":["まかせる"]},
    {"meaning":"defeat, loss, losing (a game)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"負け","answer":["まけ"]},
    {"meaning":"diligent, serious, honest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真面目","answer":["まじめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to increase, to grow","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増す","answer":["ます"]},
    {"meaning":"poor, needy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"貧しい","answer":["まずしい"]},
    {"question":"洗濯","answer":["せんたく"],"meaning":"washing; laundry"},
    {"meaning":"mistake","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"間違い","answer":["まちがい"]},
    {"meaning":"deep red, flushed (of face)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真っ赤","answer":["まっか"]},
    {"meaning":"straight (ahead), direct, upright","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真っ直ぐ","answer":["まっすぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"really, truly, entirely, completely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全く","answer":["まったく"]},
    {"meaning":"mimicry, imitation, behavior, pretense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真似","answer":["まね"]},
    {"meaning":"to invite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"招く","answer":["まねく"]},
    {"meaning":"to protect, to obey, to guard, to abide (by the rules)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"守る","answer":["まもる"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn, to revolve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回す","answer":["まわす"]},
    {"meaning":"circumference, surroundings, circulation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回り","answer":["まわり"]},
    {"meaning":"satisfaction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満足","answer":["まんぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"fruit, nut, seed, content, good result","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実","answer":["み","じつ"]},
    {"meaning":"seeing one off, farewell, escort","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"見送り","answer":["みおくり"]},
    {"meaning":"friend, ally, supporter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"味方","answer":["みかた"]},
    {"meaning":"splendid, magnificent, beautiful, admirable","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"見事","answer":["みごと"]},
    {"meaning":"to be full, to rise (tide), to mature, to expire","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満ちる","answer":["みちる"]},
    {"meaning":"to recognize, to appreciate, to approve, to admit, to notice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"認める","answer":["みとめる","したためる"]},
    {"question":"温い","answer":["ぬるい"],"meaning":"lukewarm; tepid, lenient, slow; stupid"},
    {"meaning":"enquiry, expression of sympathy, expression of concern","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見舞い","answer":["みまい"]},
    {"meaning":"present, souvenir","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"土産","answer":["みやげ"]},
    {"meaning":"capital","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"都","answer":["みやこ","と"]},
    {"meaning":"day after tomorrow","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明後日","answer":["みょうごにち","あさって"]},
    {"meaning":"future (life, tense)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"未来","answer":["みらい"]},
    {"meaning":"facing, opposite, across the street, other side","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向かい","answer":["むかい"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting, person sent to pick up an arrival","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"迎え","answer":["むかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to face","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向く","answer":["むく"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn towards, to point","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向ける","answer":["むける"]},
    {"meaning":"daze, (in a) trance, ecstasy, delirium, engrossment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夢中","answer":["むちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"clear up, clarify, define","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"明確","answer":["めいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"to order, to command, to appoint","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"命じる","answer":["めいじる"]},
    {"meaning":"(sl) meals, food","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"飯","answer":["めし"]},
    {"meaning":"face, mug, surface, facial features, mask, face guard, side or facet, corner, page","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"面","answer":["めん","おも","おもて","つら"]},
    {"meaning":"trouble, difficulty, care, attention","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"面倒","answer":["めんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"to apply for, to make an application","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申し込む","answer":["もうしこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"letter (of alphabet), character","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"文字","answer":["もじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to raise, to lift up, to flatter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"持ち上げる","answer":["もちあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to use, to make use of","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"用いる","answer":["もちいる"]},
    {"meaning":"most, extremely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最も","answer":["もっとも"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) origin, original, (2) former","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"元","answer":["もと"]},
    {"meaning":"to restore, to put back, to return","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戻す","answer":["もどす"]},
    {"meaning":"to seek, to request, to demand, to want, to wish for, to search for, to pursue (pleasure), to hunt (a job), ","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"求める","answer":["もとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"person","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"者","answer":["もの"]},
    {"meaning":"sounds","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物音","answer":["ものおと"]},
    {"meaning":"tale, story, legend","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物語","answer":["ものがたり"]},
    {"meaning":"things, everything","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物事","answer":["ものごと"]},
    {"meaning":"use, service, role, position","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役","answer":["やく","えき"]},
    {"meaning":"approximately, about, some","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"約","answer":["やく"]},
    {"meaning":"part, assigning (allotment of) parts, role, duties","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役割","answer":["やくわり"]},
    {"meaning":"inn, lodging","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"宿","answer":["やど"]},
    {"meaning":"to tear, to violate, to defeat, to smash, to destroy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"破る","answer":["やぶる"]},
    {"meaning":"to retire","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"辞める","answer":["やめる"]},
    {"meaning":"overall victory, championship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"優勝","answer":["ゆうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"friendship, fellowship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"友情","answer":["ゆうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"able, capable, efficient, skill","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"有能","answer":["ゆうのう"]},
    {"meaning":"evening","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夕べ","answer":["ゆうべ"]},
    {"meaning":"advantageous, better, profitable, lucrative","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"有利","answer":["ゆうり"]},
    {"meaning":"to permit, to allow, to approve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"許す","answer":["ゆるす"]},
    {"question":"暑い","answer":["あつい"],"meaning":"hot (weather, etc.); warm"},
    {"meaning":"dawn, daybreak","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夜明け","answer":["よあけ"]},
    {"meaning":"way, manner, kind","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"様","answer":["よう","さま"]},
    {"meaning":"easy, simple, plain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"容易","answer":["ようい"]},
    {"meaning":"season, weather, cheerfulness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"陽気","answer":["ようき"]},
    {"meaning":"request, demand, requisition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"要求","answer":["ようきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"care, precaution, guarding, caution","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"用心","answer":["ようじん"]},
    {"meaning":"aspect, state, appearance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"様子","answer":["ようす"]},
    {"meaning":"in a word, after all, the point is .., in short ..","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"要するに","answer":["ようするに"]},
    {"meaning":"gist, main point","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"要点","answer":["ようてん"]},
    {"question":"弾く","answer":["ひく","はじく"],"meaning":"to flip; to snap; to flick, to repel, to use (an abacus); to calculate, to strum; to pluck the strings (of a guitar, etc.), to play (piano, guitar)"},
    {"meaning":"expectation, assume will happen, forecast","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予期","answer":["よき"]},
    {"meaning":"to cross (e.g. arms), to traverse","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"横切る","answer":["よこぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"midnight, dead of night","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夜中","answer":["よなか","やちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"society, the world, the times","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"世の中","answer":["よのなか"]},
    {"meaning":"forecast, prediction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予報","answer":["よほう"]},
    {"meaning":"(a) joy, (a) delight, rapture, pleasure, gratification, rejoicing, congratulations, felicitations","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"喜び","answer":["よろこび"]},
    {"meaning":"comfort, ease","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"楽","answer":["らく"]},
    {"meaning":"understanding, comprehension","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"理解","answer":["りかい"]},
    {"meaning":"clever, shrewd, bright, sharp, wise, intelligent","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"利口","answer":["りこう"]},
    {"meaning":"ideal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"理想","answer":["りそう"]},
    {"meaning":"studying abroad","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留学","answer":["りゅうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"fashionable, fad, in vogue, prevailing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流行","answer":["りゅうこう","はやり"]},
    {"meaning":"fee, charge, fare","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"料金","answer":["りょうきん"]},
    {"meaning":"instance, example, case","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"例","answer":["れい","ためし"]},
    {"meaning":"expression of gratitude","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"礼","answer":["れい"]},
    {"meaning":"calm, composure, coolness, serenity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷静","answer":["れいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"queue, line, row","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"列","answer":["れつ"]},
    {"meaning":"train (ordinary)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"列車","answer":["れっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"association (of ideas), suggestion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連想","answer":["れんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"serial, consecutive, continuity, continuing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連続","answer":["れんぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"the aged, old person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"老人","answer":["ろうじん"]},
    {"meaning":"manual labor, toil, work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"労働","answer":["ろうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"to argue, to discuss, to debate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"論じる","answer":["ろんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"controversy, dispute","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"論争","answer":["ろんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"thesis, essay, treatise, paper","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"論文","answer":["ろんぶん"]},
    {"meaning":"parting, separation, farewell","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"別れ","answer":["わかれ"]},
    {"meaning":"topic, subject","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"話題","answer":["わだい"]},
    {"meaning":"laugh, laughter, smile","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"笑い","answer":["わらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to divide, to cut, to break, to halve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割る","answer":["わる"]},
    {"meaning":"abuse, insult, slander, evil speaking","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"悪口","answer":["わるくち","わるぐち","あっこう"]},
    {"question":"大勢","answer":["おおぜい","たいせい","たいぜい"],"meaning":"crowd of people; great number of people, in great numbers, general trend; current thought"},
    {"question":"傘","answer":["かさ"],"meaning":"umbrella; parasol"},
    {"question":"丈夫","answer":["じょうぶ"],"meaning":"healthy; robust; strong; solid; durable, hero; manly person; warrior"},
    {"question":"万年筆","answer":["まんねんひつ"],"meaning":"fountain pen"},
    {"meaning":"within","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"以内","answer":["いない"]},
    {"meaning":"receipt","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受付","answer":["うけつけ"]},
    {"question":"お菓子","answer":["おかし"],"meaning":"confections; sweets; candy"},
    {"question":"雲","answer":["くも"],"meaning":"cloud"},
    {"question":"涼しい","answer":["すずしい"],"meaning":"cool; refreshing, clear (e.g. eyes); bright, clear; distinct, composed (facial expression); unruffled; unconcerned, pure; upright; innocent"},
    {"question":"池","answer":["いけ"],"meaning":"pond"},
    {"question":"泳ぐ","answer":["およぐ"],"meaning":"to swim"},
    {"question":"汚い","answer":["きたない"],"meaning":"dirty; filthy; foul; unclean, disordered; messy; untidy; poor (e.g. handwriting), indecent (language, etc.); dirty; vulgar; coarse, dastardly; mean; base; underhanded, stingy; greedy"},
    {"meaning":"(polite) your house","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お宅","answer":["おたく"]},
    {"question":"曇る","answer":["くもる"],"meaning":"to get cloudy; to cloud over; to become overcast, to cloud up; to fog up; to mist up; to become dim, to be gloomy; to be clouded (expression); to be downcast, to look slightly downward (of a noh mask; indicating sadness, grief, etc.), to mumble; to mutter"},
    {"meaning":"husband","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夫","answer":["おっと"]},
    {"meaning":"to drop","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落とす","answer":["おとす"]},
    {"meaning":"calling on someone who is ill, enquiry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お見舞い","answer":["おみまい"]},
    {"meaning":"souvenir","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お土産","answer":["おみやげ"]},
    {"meaning":"to break or to fold","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"折る","answer":["おる"]},
    {"question":"曇り","answer":["くもり"],"meaning":"cloudiness; cloudy weather; shadow"},
    {"meaning":"to break or be folded","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"折れる","answer":["おれる"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"会議","answer":["かいぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"会議室","answer":["かいぎしつ"]},
    {"question":"黒板","answer":["こくばん"],"meaning":"blackboard"},
    {"meaning":"science","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"科学","answer":["かがく"]},
    {"question":"鬼","answer":["おに"],"meaning":"oni; ogre; demon, spirit of a deceased person, ogre-like person (i.e. fierce, relentless, merciless, etc.), it (in a game of tag, hide-and-seek, etc.), Chinese \"ghost\" constellation (one of the 28 mansions), very; extremely; super-"},
    {"meaning":"shape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"形","answer":["かたち"]},
    {"question":"高価","answer":["こうか"],"meaning":"high price"},
    {"meaning":"housewife","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"家内","answer":["かない"]},
    {"question":"騒音","answer":["そうおん"],"meaning":"noise"},
    {"meaning":"certainly, necessarily","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"必ず","answer":["かならず"]},
    {"question":"騒ぎ","answer":["さわぎ"],"meaning":"uproar; disturbance"},
    {"meaning":"hair","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"髪","answer":["かみ"]},
    {"question":"駄目","answer":["だめ"],"meaning":"no good; not serving its purpose; useless; broken, hopeless; wasted; in vain; purposeless, cannot; must not; not allowed, neutral point (in go); intersection owned by neither player at the end of a game"},
    {"question":"馬鹿","answer":["ばか"],"meaning":"fool; idiot, trivial matter; folly; absurdity, foolish; stupid; dull; absurd; ridiculous, Mactra chinensis (species of trough shell)"},
    {"question":"飽きる","answer":["あきる"],"meaning":"to get tired of; to lose interest in; to have enough"},
    {"meaning":"relationship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関係","answer":["かんけい"]},
    {"meaning":"opportunity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"機会","answer":["きかい"]},
    {"question":"食糧","answer":["しょくりょう"],"meaning":"food (esp. staple food such as rice or wheat); provisions; rations; food supply"},
    {"question":"食卓","answer":["しょくたく"],"meaning":"dining table"},
    {"question":"食う","answer":["くう"],"meaning":"to eat, to live; to make a living; to survive, to bite; to sting (as insects do), to tease; to torment; to taunt; to make light of; to make fun of, to encroach on; to eat into; to consume, to defeat a superior; to threaten a position, to consume time and-or resources, to receive something (usu. an unfavourable event), to have sexual relations with a woman, esp. for the first time"},
    {"question":"額","answer":["ひたい","がく"],"meaning":"picture (framed), amount or sum (of money), forehead; brow"},
    {"meaning":"education","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"教育","answer":["きょういく"]},
    {"meaning":"neighbourhood","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"近所","answer":["きんじょ"]},
    {"question":"頬","answer":["ほお","ほほ"],"meaning":"cheek (of face), face; mug, surface, surrounding area, cheek; cheeks"},
    {"meaning":"airport","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"空港","answer":["くうこう"]},
    {"question":"預ける","answer":["あずける"],"meaning":"to give into custody; to leave (a child) in the care of; to entrust; to deposit, to lean on; to put one's weight on"},
    {"question":"順調","answer":["じゅんちょう"],"meaning":"favourable; favorable; doing well; OK; all right"},
    {"meaning":"to get dark, to come to an end","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暮れる","answer":["くれる"]},
    {"meaning":"finance, economy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経済","answer":["けいざい"]},
    {"meaning":"police","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"警察","answer":["けいさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"scene, landscape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"景色","answer":["けしき"]},
    {"question":"順番","answer":["じゅんばん"],"meaning":"turn (in line); order of things; sequential order"},
    {"meaning":"lodging","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"下宿","answer":["げしゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"never","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決して","answer":["けっして"]},
    {"meaning":"cause, source","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原因","answer":["げんいん"]},
    {"question":"霜","answer":["しも"],"meaning":"frost"},
    {"meaning":"high school","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"高等学校","answer":["こうとうがっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"government worker","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公務員","answer":["こうむいん"]},
    {"meaning":"international","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"国際","answer":["こくさい"]},
    {"meaning":"(honorable) your husband","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御主人","answer":["ごしゅじん"]},
    {"meaning":"knowing, acquaintance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"ご存じ","answer":["ごぞんじ"]},
    {"question":"需要","answer":["じゅよう"],"meaning":"demand; request"},
    {"meaning":"uncooked rice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"米","answer":["こめ"]},
    {"question":"電子","answer":["でんし"],"meaning":"electron, electronic"},
    {"meaning":"latest, nowadays","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最近","answer":["さいきん"]},
    {"meaning":"last, end","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最後","answer":["さいご"]},
    {"meaning":"beginning, first","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最初","answer":["さいしょ"]},
    {"question":"雷","answer":["かみなり","いかずち","いかづち"],"meaning":"lightning; thunder; thunderbolt, god of thunder; god of lightning, anger; fit of anger, thunder"},
    {"meaning":"(polite) to give","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差し上げる","answer":["さしあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"industry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"産業","answer":["さんぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"disappointment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残念","answer":["ざんねん"]},
    {"meaning":"city","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"市","answer":["し","いち"]},
    {"question":"雰囲気","answer":["ふんいき"],"meaning":"mood; ambience; ambiance; aura; feel, a certain air; presence; special aura; something (about someone), air; atmosphere"},
    {"meaning":"failure, mistake","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"失敗","answer":["しっぱい"]},
    {"meaning":"citizen","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"市民","answer":["しみん"]},
    {"meaning":"office","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"事務所","answer":["じむしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"freedom","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自由","answer":["じゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"custom, manners","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"習慣","answer":["しゅうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"an address, a residence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"住所","answer":["じゅうしょ"]},
    {"question":"離婚","answer":["りこん"],"meaning":"divorce"},
    {"meaning":"woman","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"女性","answer":["じょせい"]},
    {"meaning":"to investigate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"調べる","answer":["しらべる"]},
    {"meaning":"Shinto shrine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"神社","answer":["じんじゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"swimming","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"水泳","answer":["すいえい"]},
    {"question":"離れる","answer":["はなれる"],"meaning":"to be separated; to be apart; to be distant, to leave; to go away, to leave (a job, etc.); to quit; to give up, to lose connection with; to drift away from"},
    {"meaning":"to exceed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過ぎる","answer":["すぎる"]},
    {"question":"離す","answer":["はなす"],"meaning":"to separate; to part; to divide; to keep apart"},
    {"meaning":"to finish","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"済む","answer":["すむ"]},
    {"question":"集団","answer":["しゅうだん"],"meaning":"group; mass"},
    {"question":"隠れる","answer":["かくれる"],"meaning":"to hide; to be hidden; to conceal oneself; to disappear"},
    {"question":"隠す","answer":["かくす"],"meaning":"to hide; to conceal"},
    {"question":"障害","answer":["しょうがい"],"meaning":"obstacle; impediment; hindrance; difficulty; barrier, handicap; impairment; disability; disorder; malfunction"},
    {"question":"随分","answer":["ずいぶん"],"meaning":"very; extremely; surprisingly; considerably, contemptible; reprehensible"},
    {"meaning":"war","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戦争","answer":["せんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"to rear, to bring up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"育てる","answer":["そだてる"]},
    {"meaning":"grandfather","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"祖父","answer":["そふ"]},
    {"meaning":"grandmother","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"祖母","answer":["そぼ"]},
    {"question":"隅","answer":["すみ"],"meaning":"corner; nook; recess"},
    {"meaning":"to break down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"倒れる","answer":["たおれる"]},
    {"meaning":"definite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確か","answer":["たしか"]},
    {"meaning":"to visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"訪ねる","answer":["たずねる"]},
    {"meaning":"for example","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"例えば","answer":["たとえば"]},
    {"meaning":"male","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"男性","answer":["だんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"to seize","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"捕まえる","answer":["つかまえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be attached","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付く","answer":["つく"]},
    {"meaning":"circumstances, convenience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"都合","answer":["つごう"]},
    {"question":"陰","answer":["かげ","いん"],"meaning":"unseen location (i.e. somewhere private), shade; shadow, other side; back; background, yin (i.e. the negative)"},
    {"question":"鎖","answer":["くさり"],"meaning":"chain; chains"},
    {"question":"鍵","answer":["かぎ","けん"],"meaning":"key, lock, key (of a piano, etc.)"},
    {"meaning":"(humble) wife","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"妻","answer":["つま"]},
    {"meaning":"to lead","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連れる","answer":["つれる"]},
    {"meaning":"suitability","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適当","answer":["てきとう"]},
    {"question":"鍋","answer":["なべ"],"meaning":"saucepan; pot, stew; hot pot"},
    {"question":"鋭い","answer":["するどい"],"meaning":"sharp (blade); pointed, sharp (pain); stabbing; cutting (remark); stinging; pointed (question or look); screeching (noise), perceptive; keen; quick (mind); astute; shrewd; discerning, nimble; agile; quick"},
    {"meaning":"weather forecast","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"天気予報","answer":["てんきよほう"]},
    {"meaning":"telegram","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"電報","answer":["でんぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"tool, means","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"道具","answer":["どうぐ"]},
    {"question":"銅貨","answer":["どうか"],"meaning":"copper coin"},
    {"question":"銃","answer":["じゅう"],"meaning":"gun; rifle; small arms"},
    {"meaning":"on the way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"途中","answer":["とちゅう","つちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to fix, to repair","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直す","answer":["なおす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be fixed, to be repaired","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直る","answer":["なおる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be cured, to heal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"治る","answer":["なおる"]},
    {"meaning":"to die","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"亡くなる","answer":["なくなる"]},
    {"meaning":"to throw or cast away","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"投げる","answer":["なげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to sound","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"鳴る","answer":["なる"]},
    {"meaning":"to grow accustomed to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"慣れる","answer":["なれる"]},
    {"meaning":"bitter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦い","answer":["にがい"]},
    {"meaning":"to escape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"逃げる","answer":["にげる"]},
    {"question":"鉄道","answer":["てつどう"],"meaning":"railroad; railway; rail transport"},
    {"question":"鉄","answer":["てつ","くろがね"],"meaning":"money, metal, iron (Fe), strong and hard (as iron), railway, railway enthusiast, iron"},
    {"meaning":"doll, figure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人形","answer":["にんぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to steal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"盗む","answer":["ぬすむ"]},
    {"meaning":"fever","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"熱","answer":["ねつ"]},
    {"question":"釣り","answer":["つり"],"meaning":"fishing; angling, change (e.g. for a purchase), trolling; writing false posts online"},
    {"question":"金属","answer":["きんぞく"],"meaning":"metal"},
    {"question":"量","answer":["りょう"],"meaning":"quantity; amount; volume; portion (of food), progress"},
    {"question":"重視","answer":["じゅうし"],"meaning":"importance; stress; serious consideration, to take something seriously; to attach importance; to stress"},
    {"question":"郵便","answer":["ゆうびん"],"meaning":"mail service; postal service; mail; post, mail; postal matter; postal items"},
    {"meaning":"situation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"場合","answer":["ばあい"]},
    {"meaning":"dentist","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"歯医者","answer":["はいしゃ"]},
    {"question":"部分","answer":["ぶぶん"],"meaning":"portion; section; part"},
    {"question":"選択","answer":["せんたく"],"meaning":"selection; choice; option"},
    {"question":"道徳","answer":["どうとく"],"meaning":"morals"},
    {"question":"逮捕","answer":["たいほ"],"meaning":"arrest; apprehension; capture"},
    {"meaning":"opposition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反対","answer":["はんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to grow cold","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷える","answer":["ひえる"]},
    {"question":"途端","answer":["とたん"],"meaning":"just (now, at the moment, etc.); just as; in the act of; as soon as; at the moment that"},
    {"question":"逆","answer":["ぎゃく"],"meaning":"reverse; opposite, converse (of a hypothesis, etc.), inverse (function), inverse; reverse"},
    {"question":"退屈","answer":["たいくつ"],"meaning":"tedium; boredom"},
    {"question":"迷惑","answer":["めいわく"],"meaning":"trouble; bother; annoyance"},
    {"question":"近頃","answer":["ちかごろ"],"meaning":"lately; recently; nowadays"},
    {"meaning":"art gallery","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"美術館","answer":["びじゅつかん"]},
    {"meaning":"extremely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"非常に","answer":["ひじょうに"]},
    {"meaning":"to move house","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引っ越す","answer":["ひっこす"]},
    {"meaning":"necessary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"必要","answer":["ひつよう"]},
    {"meaning":"to increase","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増える","answer":["ふえる"]},
    {"question":"辛い","answer":["つらい","からい"],"meaning":"spicy; hot, salty, harsh (criticism); severe (punishment); strict, painful; bitter; difficult; tough, painful; bitter; heart-breaking; difficult (emotionally), tough; difficult; hard (usu. of situations), cruel; harsh; cold, difficult to ...; hard to ..."},
    {"question":"輸出","answer":["ゆしゅつ"],"meaning":"export, efferent"},
    {"question":"輸入","answer":["ゆにゅう"],"meaning":"importation; import; introduction, afferent"},
    {"meaning":"inconvenience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不便","answer":["ふべん","ふびん"]},
    {"question":"軒","answer":["のき","けん"],"meaning":"eaves, narrow aisle surrounding the core of a temple building, counter for buildings (esp. houses), suffix for a pen name, stage name, etc."},
    {"question":"軍隊","answer":["ぐんたい"],"meaning":"armed forces; military; troops"},
    {"meaning":"grammar","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"文法","answer":["ぶんぽう"]},
    {"question":"身長","answer":["しんちょう"],"meaning":"height (of body); stature"},
    {"meaning":"reply","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"返事","answer":["へんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"(humble) to go, to come","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"参る","answer":["まいる"]},
    {"question":"身体","answer":["しんたい","からだ"],"meaning":"body, torso; trunk, build; physique; constitution, health, corpse; dead body, body; physical system; person"},
    {"meaning":"to make a mistake","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"間違える","answer":["まちがえる"]},
    {"question":"身","answer":["み"],"meaning":"body, oneself, one's place; one's position, main part; meat (as opposed to bone, skin, etc.); wood (as opposed to bark); blade (as opposed to its handle); container (as opposed to its lid), (dead) body; corpse"},
    {"meaning":"to go around","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回る","answer":["まわる"]},
    {"meaning":"harbour","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"港","answer":["みなと"]},
    {"question":"跡","answer":["あと"],"meaning":"trace; tracks; mark; sign, site; remains; ruins, scar, trace"},
    {"meaning":"to go out to meet","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"迎える","answer":["むかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"olden days, former","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"昔","answer":["むかし"]},
    {"question":"贅沢","answer":["ぜいたく"],"meaning":"luxury; extravagance, to live in luxury; to indulge oneself, lavish (use of something); abundant; copious; wasteful"},
    {"question":"賞","answer":["しょう"],"meaning":"prize; award"},
    {"meaning":"(humble) to say, to tell","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申し上げる","answer":["もうしあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"(humble) to be called, to say","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申す","answer":["もうす"]},
    {"question":"賛成","answer":["さんせい"],"meaning":"approval; agreement; support; favour; favor"},
    {"question":"資源","answer":["しげん"],"meaning":"resources"},
    {"question":"貴重","answer":["きちょう"],"meaning":"precious; valuable"},
    {"question":"貯金","answer":["ちょきん"],"meaning":"putting money aside; savings; deposit (e.g. in a bank), accumulated surplus of wins; wins in the bank"},
    {"question":"販売","answer":["はんばい"],"meaning":"sales; selling; marketing"},
    {"question":"貢献","answer":["こうけん"],"meaning":"contribution (furthering a goal or cause); services (to a cause)"},
    {"meaning":"preparation for a lesson","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予習","answer":["よしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"arrangement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予定","answer":["よてい"]},
    {"meaning":"reservation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予約","answer":["よやく"]},
    {"meaning":"to visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寄る","answer":["よる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be delighted","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"喜ぶ","answer":["よろこぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"reason","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"理由","answer":["りゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"utilization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"利用","answer":["りよう"]},
    {"meaning":"both sides","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"両方","answer":["りょうほう"]},
    {"meaning":"absence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留守","answer":["るす"]},
    {"question":"豪華","answer":["ごうか"],"meaning":"wonderful; gorgeous; splendor; splendour; pomp; extravagance"},
    {"question":"豆","answer":["まめ"],"meaning":"legume (esp. edible legumes or their seeds, such as beans, peas, pulses, etc.); beans; peas, soya bean (Glycine max); soybean; soy, female genitalia (esp. the clitoris), kidney, miniature; tiny, child"},
    {"meaning":"rate, ratio, percentage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割合","answer":["わりあい"]},
    {"meaning":"to break","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割れる","answer":["われる"]},
    {"meaning":"way of swimming","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"泳ぎ方","answer":["およぎかた"]},
    {"question":"譲る","answer":["ゆずる"],"meaning":"to turn over; to assign; to hand over; to transmit; to convey; to sell; to dispose of, to yield; to surrender; to concede"},
    {"question":"一生","answer":["いっしょう"],"meaning":"whole life; a lifetime; all through life; one existence; a generation; an age; the whole world; the era, (the only, the greatest, etc.) of one's life"},
    {"question":"一瞬","answer":["いっしゅん"],"meaning":"instant; moment; for an instant"},
    {"question":"一致","answer":["いっち"],"meaning":"coincidence; agreement; union; match, conformity; consistency, cooperation"},
    {"question":"謎","answer":["なぞ"],"meaning":"riddle; puzzle; enigma; mystery, enigmatic; mysterious"},
    {"question":"下す","answer":["くだす"],"meaning":"to make a decision; to draw a conclusion, to give a judgement; to hand down a verdict; to pass a sentence; to give an order, to let go down; to lower, to do oneself; to do by oneself, to beat; to defeat, to have loose bowels; to have diarrhea, to pass (in stool); to discharge from the body, to do in one go; to do to the end without stopping"},
    {"question":"不可","answer":["ふか"],"meaning":"wrong; bad; improper; unjustifiable; inadvisable, not allowed; not possible, failing grade"},
    {"question":"世紀","answer":["せいき"],"meaning":"century; era"},
    {"question":"丘","answer":["おか"],"meaning":"hill; height; knoll; rising ground, bonus points awarded to the winner at the end of a game, mound; hill"},
    {"question":"諦める","answer":["あきらめる"],"meaning":"to give up; to abandon (hope, plans); to resign oneself (to)"},
    {"question":"中央","answer":["ちゅうおう"],"meaning":"centre; center; middle; heart, metropolis; capital city; central government"},
    {"question":"主張","answer":["しゅちょう"],"meaning":"claim; request; insistence; assertion; advocacy; emphasis; contention; opinion; tenet"},
    {"question":"主義","answer":["しゅぎ"],"meaning":"doctrine; rule; principle; -ism"},
    {"question":"予測","answer":["よそく"],"meaning":"prediction; estimation"},
    {"question":"予算","answer":["よさん"],"meaning":"estimate; budget"},
    {"question":"予防","answer":["よぼう"],"meaning":"prevention; precaution; protection against"},
    {"question":"事態","answer":["じたい"],"meaning":"situation; (present) state of affairs; circumstances"},
    {"question":"二十（歳）","answer":["はたち"]},
    {"question":"交換","answer":["こうかん"],"meaning":"exchange; interchange; switching; reciprocity; barter; substitution; replacement; clearing (of checks, cheques)"},
    {"question":"人気","answer":["にんき","ひとけ"],"meaning":"popularity; public favor, condition (e.g. market); tone; character; nature, sign of life; human presence, humanity; humaneness, prevailing mood of a locality; emotional climate of a district"},
    {"question":"今後","answer":["こんご"],"meaning":"from now on; hereafter"},
    {"question":"請求","answer":["せいきゅう"],"meaning":"claim; demand; charge; application; request; billing (for a service)"},
    {"question":"企業","answer":["きぎょう"],"meaning":"enterprise; undertaking; corporation; business"},
    {"question":"休憩","answer":["きゅうけい"],"meaning":"rest; break; recess; intermission"},
    {"question":"休暇","answer":["きゅうか"],"meaning":"holiday; day off; furlough; absence (from work)"},
    {"question":"伝統","answer":["でんとう"],"meaning":"tradition; convention"},
    {"question":"伸ばす","answer":["のばす"],"meaning":"to grow long (e.g. hair, nails), to lengthen; to extend; to stretch, to reach out; to hold out, to straighten; to smooth out, to spread evenly (dough, cream, etc.), to dilute; to thin out, to postpone, to prolong, to strengthen; to develop; to expand"},
    {"question":"伸びる","answer":["のびる"],"meaning":"to stretch; to extend; to lengthen; to spread, to make progress; to grow (beard, body height), to grow stale (soba), to be straightened; to be flattened; to be smoothed, to be exhausted"},
    {"question":"調査","answer":["ちょうさ"],"meaning":"investigation; examination; inquiry; enquiry; survey"},
    {"question":"体温","answer":["たいおん"],"meaning":"temperature; body temperature (human, animal)"},
    {"question":"余分","answer":["よぶん"],"meaning":"extra; excess; surplus"},
    {"question":"余裕","answer":["よゆう"],"meaning":"surplus; margin; leeway; room; time; allowance; flexibility; scope; rope, composure; placidity; complacency; calm"},
    {"question":"読書","answer":["どくしょ"],"meaning":"reading"},
    {"question":"価値","answer":["かち"],"meaning":"value; worth; merit"},
    {"question":"価格","answer":["かかく"],"meaning":"price; value; cost"},
    {"question":"保存","answer":["ほぞん"],"meaning":"preservation; conservation; storage; saving (e.g. to disk); maintenance"},
    {"question":"保証","answer":["ほしょう"],"meaning":"guarantee; security; assurance; pledge; warranty"},
    {"question":"信仰","answer":["しんこう"],"meaning":"(religious) faith; belief; creed"},
    {"question":"修正","answer":["しゅうせい"],"meaning":"amendment; correction; revision; modification; alteration; retouching; update; fix"},
    {"question":"修理","answer":["しゅうり"],"meaning":"repairing; mending; servicing"},
    {"question":"俳優","answer":["はいゆう"],"meaning":"actor; actress; player; performer"},
    {"question":"個人","answer":["こじん"],"meaning":"individual; private person; personal; private"},
    {"question":"語学","answer":["ごがく"],"meaning":"language study"},
    {"question":"停留所","answer":["ていりゅうじょ"],"meaning":"bus stop; tram stop; stop; station"},
    {"question":"健康","answer":["けんこう"],"meaning":"health; sound; wholesome"},
    {"question":"傷","answer":["きず"],"meaning":"wound; injury; cut; gash; bruise; scratch; scrape; scar, chip; crack; scratch; nick, flaw; defect; weakness; weak point, stain (on one's reputation); disgrace; dishonor; dishonour, (emotional) hurt; hurt feelings"},
    {"question":"語る","answer":["かたる"],"meaning":"to talk about; to speak of; to tell; to narrate, to recite; to chant, to indicate; to show"},
    {"question":"優秀","answer":["ゆうしゅう"],"meaning":"superiority; excellence"},
    {"question":"先日","answer":["せんじつ"],"meaning":"the other day; a few days ago"},
    {"question":"克服","answer":["こくふく"],"meaning":"conquest (of a difficulty, illness, handicap, etc.); overcoming; bringing under control; subjugation; victory over"},
    {"question":"免許","answer":["めんきょ"],"meaning":"license; permit; licence; certificate"},
    {"question":"典型","answer":["てんけい"],"meaning":"type; pattern; model; epitome; exemplar; archetypal; representative"},
    {"question":"誘う","answer":["さそう","いざなう"],"meaning":"to invite; to ask; to call (for), to tempt; to lure; to induce"},
    {"question":"冒険","answer":["ぼうけん"],"meaning":"risk; venture; adventure"},
    {"question":"冗談","answer":["じょうだん"],"meaning":"jest; joke; funny story"},
    {"question":"誕生","answer":["たんじょう"],"meaning":"birth; creation; formation"},
    {"question":"誇り","answer":["ほこり"],"meaning":"pride; boast"},
    {"question":"出身","answer":["しゅっしん"],"meaning":"person's origin (e.g. city, country, parentage, school)"},
    {"question":"刀","answer":["かたな","とう"],"meaning":"(single-edged) sword; katana, dagger; knife, scalpel"},
    {"question":"分ける","answer":["わける"],"meaning":"to divide (into); to split (into); to part; to separate; to divide up; to classify; to sort out; to divide out, to share; to distribute; to deal out; to dish out, to distinguish; to discriminate; to differentiate (between), to break up (a fight); to mediate, to call a draw; to tie, to push one's way through (a crowd), to sell"},
    {"question":"分析","answer":["ぶんせき"],"meaning":"analysis"},
    {"question":"分野","answer":["ぶんや"],"meaning":"field; sphere; realm; division; branch"},
    {"question":"刑事","answer":["けいじ"],"meaning":"(police) detective, criminal matter"},
    {"question":"利益","answer":["りえき"],"meaning":"profit; gains, benefit; advantage; interest (of the public, etc.), grace (of God, Buddha, etc.) (esp. as attained through rightful actions, prayer, adherence to one's faith, etc.); blessing; miracle"},
    {"question":"券","answer":["けん"],"meaning":"ticket; coupon; bond; certificate"},
    {"question":"刺激","answer":["しげき"],"meaning":"stimulus; impetus; incentive; encouragement; motivation; provocation; excitement; thrill"},
    {"question":"詳しい","answer":["くわしい"],"meaning":"detailed; full; accurate, knowing very well; well-acquainted; well-informed"},
    {"question":"加減","answer":["かげん"],"meaning":"degree; extent; just right amount of, condition; state of health, adjustment; moderation, addition and subtraction"},
    {"question":"効く","answer":["きく"],"meaning":"to be effective; to show effect, to do its work; to carry out its function well, to be possible to use"},
    {"question":"効果","answer":["こうか"],"meaning":"effect; effectiveness; efficacy; result, effects (e.g. sound effects, visual effects, special effects)"},
    {"question":"詩人","answer":["しじん"],"meaning":"poet"},
    {"question":"詩","answer":["し"],"meaning":"modern poetry, poem; verse of poetry"},
    {"question":"評判","answer":["ひょうばん"],"meaning":"fame; reputation; popularity, rumour (rumor); talk"},
    {"question":"勤める","answer":["つとめる"],"meaning":"to work (for); to be employed (at); to serve (in), to serve (as); to act (as); to fill (the position of); to play the role (of), to conduct a religious service"},
    {"question":"勧める","answer":["すすめる"],"meaning":"to recommend; to advise; to encourage; to offer (wine)"},
    {"question":"匂い","answer":["におい"],"meaning":"odour; odor; scent; smell; stench, aura; whiff; smacks of ...; sense; flavour; flavor"},
    {"question":"包み","answer":["つつみ"],"meaning":"bundle; package; parcel, counter for wrapped objects"},
    {"question":"化粧","answer":["けしょう"],"meaning":"make-up; makeup; cosmetics"},
    {"question":"評価","answer":["ひょうか"],"meaning":"valuation; estimation; assessment; evaluation; rating, to value; to assess; to rate; to estimate value, to appreciate; to value highly; to acknowledge the value (of something)"},
    {"question":"証明","answer":["しょうめい"],"meaning":"proof; verification; certification"},
    {"question":"半ば","answer":["なかば"],"meaning":"middle; half; semi; halfway; partly"},
    {"question":"協力","answer":["きょうりょく"],"meaning":"cooperation; collaboration"},
    {"question":"診察","answer":["しんさつ"],"meaning":"medical examination"},
    {"question":"博士","answer":["はかせ","はくし"],"meaning":"doctorate; PhD; Dr (as a title), expert; learned person"},
    {"question":"博物館","answer":["はくぶつかん"],"meaning":"museum"},
    {"question":"訴える","answer":["うったえる"],"meaning":"to raise; to bring to (someone's attention), to appeal to (reason, emotions, etc.); to work on (one's emotions); to play on (one's sympathies), to complain, to sue (a person); to take someone to court, to resort to (e.g. arms, violence)"},
    {"question":"設計","answer":["せっけい"],"meaning":"plan; design; layout"},
    {"question":"記憶","answer":["きおく"],"meaning":"memory; recollection; remembrance, storage"},
    {"question":"計算","answer":["けいさん"],"meaning":"calculation; reckoning; count, forecast"},
    {"question":"危ない","answer":["あぶない"],"meaning":"dangerous; risky; hazardous; perilous; precarious, in danger; in jeopardy; critical; grave; at risk, uncertain; unreliable; insecure; unsteady; doubtful, close (i.e. a close call); narrow, look out!; watch out!"},
    {"question":"卵","answer":["たまご"],"meaning":"eggs; egg; spawn; roe, hen egg, (an expert) in the making, beginning; origin; infancy, egg; eggshell, ovum; ovule; egg cell"},
    {"question":"厄介","answer":["やっかい"],"meaning":"trouble; burden; nuisance; bother; worry, care; dependence; support; kindness; obligation; staying (with a person)"},
    {"question":"厚い","answer":["あつい"],"meaning":"thick; deep; heavy, kind; cordial; hospitable; warm; faithful, abundant"},
    {"question":"及ぼす","answer":["およぼす"],"meaning":"to exert; to cause; to exercise"},
    {"question":"友人","answer":["ゆうじん"],"meaning":"friend"},
    {"question":"触れる","answer":["ふれる"],"meaning":"to touch; to feel, to experience; to come in contact with; to be emotionally moved (by); to perceive, to touch on a subject; to allude to, to be in conflict (with); to violate (law, copyright, etc.), to proclaim"},
    {"question":"反抗","answer":["はんこう"],"meaning":"opposition; resistance; insubordination; defiance; hostility; rebellion"},
    {"question":"収穫","answer":["しゅうかく"],"meaning":"harvest; crop; ingathering, fruits (of one's labors); results"},
    {"question":"叫ぶ","answer":["さけぶ"],"meaning":"to shout; to cry; to scream; to shriek; to yell; to exclaim, to clamor (for or against); to clamour (for or against)"},
    {"question":"可能","answer":["かのう"],"meaning":"potential; possible; practicable; feasible"},
    {"question":"叱る","answer":["しかる"],"meaning":"to scold; to chide; to rebuke; to reprimand"},
    {"question":"同僚","answer":["どうりょう"],"meaning":"coworker; co-worker; colleague; associate"},
    {"question":"名人","answer":["めいじん"],"meaning":"master; expert"},
    {"question":"吐く","answer":["はく"],"meaning":"to breathe out; to breathe, to tell (a lie); to use (foul language), to vomit; to throw up; to spit up, to vomit; to throw up; to spit up, to emit; to send forth; to breathe out, to give (an opinion); to make (a comment); to express; to tell, to confess"},
    {"question":"含む","answer":["ふくむ"],"meaning":"to contain; to comprise; to have; to hold; to include; to embrace, to hold in the mouth, to bear in mind; to understand; to harbor (grudge, etc.); to harbour, to express (emotion, etc.); to imply"},
    {"question":"周囲","answer":["しゅうい"],"meaning":"surroundings; environs, circumference"},
    {"question":"命令","answer":["めいれい"],"meaning":"order; command; decree; directive, (software) instruction; statement"},
    {"question":"哀れ","answer":["あわれ"],"meaning":"pity; sorrow; grief; misery; compassion; pathos, pitiable; pitiful; pathetic; miserable, alack; alas"},
    {"question":"哲学","answer":["てつがく"],"meaning":"philosophy"},
    {"question":"唯一","answer":["ゆいいつ"],"meaning":"only; sole; unique"},
    {"question":"喫茶店","answer":["きっさてん"],"meaning":"coffee shop; tearoom; coffee lounge; coffeehouse; cafe"},
    {"question":"営業","answer":["えいぎょう"],"meaning":"business; trade; sales; operations"},
    {"question":"器用","answer":["きよう"],"meaning":"skilful; skillfull; adroit; dexterous; dextrous; deft; nimble; handy, clever; shrewd; ingenious"},
    {"question":"回復","answer":["かいふく"],"meaning":"restoration; rehabilitation; recovery; return; replevin; improvement, recovery (from an illness); recuperation; convalescence"},
    {"question":"団体","answer":["だんたい"],"meaning":"organization; organisation; association"},
    {"question":"囲む","answer":["かこむ"],"meaning":"to surround; to encircle; to enclose; to fence; to wall in, to besiege; to lay siege to, to play (go, shogi, etc.)"},
    {"question":"解釈","answer":["かいしゃく"],"meaning":"explanation; interpretation"},
    {"question":"国語","answer":["こくご"],"meaning":"national language, Japanese language (often as a school subject in Japan), native Japanese words (as opposed to loanwords)"},
    {"question":"角","answer":["カク","かど","つの"],"meaning":"angle, square (or cube), bishop, third degree (of the Japanese & Chinese pentatonic scale), Chinese \"horn\" constellation (one of the 28 mansions), jiao (monetary unit of China; one-tenth of a yuan), corner (e.g. desk, pavement), edge, horn, corner; nook; recess, downstage right (on a noh stage)"},
    {"question":"親戚","answer":["しんせき"],"meaning":"relative; relation; kin"},
    {"question":"地平線","answer":["ちへいせん"],"meaning":"horizon (related to land)"},
    {"question":"城","answer":["しろ"],"meaning":"castle, castle (in place names), fortress (surrounded by a wall, moat, etc.)"},
    {"question":"基本","answer":["きほん"],"meaning":"foundation; basis; standard"},
    {"question":"塀","answer":["へい"],"meaning":"wall, fence"},
    {"question":"覚悟","answer":["かくご"],"meaning":"resolution; resignation; readiness; preparedness"},
    {"question":"塩","answer":["しお","えん"],"meaning":"salt (i.e. sodium chloride); common salt; table salt, salt (e.g. sodium chloride, calcium sulfate, etc.), hardship; toil; trouble, saltiness"},
    {"question":"覆う","answer":["おおう"],"meaning":"to cover; to hide; to conceal; to wrap; to disguise"},
    {"question":"墓","answer":["はか"],"meaning":"gravesite; tomb"},
    {"question":"外す","answer":["はずす"],"meaning":"to unfasten; to undo, to remove; to take off; to deinstall, to leave; to step out; to slip away, to miss (a target)"},
    {"question":"外出","answer":["がいしゅつ"],"meaning":"going out; outing; leaving (one's home, office, etc.)"},
    {"question":"大した","answer":["たいした"],"meaning":"considerable; great; important; significant; a big deal"},
    {"question":"大半","answer":["たいはん"],"meaning":"majority; more than half; most (of), mostly; largely; mainly; predominately; nearly"},
    {"question":"大抵","answer":["たいてい"],"meaning":"mostly; ordinarily; usually; generally, probably, most; almost all, ordinary, proper; appropriate; moderate"},
    {"question":"大気","answer":["たいき"],"meaning":"atmosphere"},
    {"question":"大統領","answer":["だいとうりょう"],"meaning":"president; chief executive"},
    {"question":"要素","answer":["ようそ"],"meaning":"component; factor; item (e.g. in list), element (e.g. in array); member (e.g. data structure)"},
    {"question":"大部分","answer":["だいぶぶん"],"meaning":"most part; greater part; majority"},
    {"question":"要る","answer":["いる"],"meaning":"to need; to want"},
    {"question":"奇妙","answer":["きみょう"],"meaning":"strange; queer; curious"},
    {"question":"契約","answer":["けいやく"],"meaning":"contract; compact; agreement"},
    {"question":"奥","answer":["おく"],"meaning":"inner part; inside; interior; depths (e.g. of a forest); back (of a house, drawer, etc.); bottom (e.g. of one's heart); recesses; heart"},
    {"question":"奨学金","answer":["しょうがくきん"],"meaning":"scholarship; stipend; bursary, student loan"},
    {"question":"奪う","answer":["うばう"],"meaning":"to snatch away; to dispossess; to steal"},
    {"question":"女子","answer":["じょし","おなご","めこ"],"meaning":"woman; girl"},
    {"question":"妙","answer":["みょう"],"meaning":"strange; weird; odd; curious, wonder; mystery; miracle; excellence, cleverness; adroitness; knack; skill"},
    {"question":"委員","answer":["いいん"],"meaning":"committee member"},
    {"question":"姿","answer":["すがた"],"meaning":"figure; form; shape, appearance; dress; guise, state; condition; picture; image, form (of a waka), dressed in ...; wearing ..."},
    {"question":"嫁","answer":["よめ"],"meaning":"wife; bride, (one's) daughter-in-law"},
    {"question":"嫌う","answer":["きらう"],"meaning":"to hate; to dislike; to loathe"},
    {"question":"学ぶ","answer":["まなぶ"],"meaning":"to study (in depth); to learn; to take lessons in"},
    {"question":"褒める","answer":["ほめる"],"meaning":"to praise; to admire; to speak well of someone"},
    {"question":"宇宙","answer":["うちゅう"],"meaning":"universe; cosmos; space"},
    {"question":"完了","answer":["かんりょう"],"meaning":"completion; conclusion, perfect (tense, form, aspect), end; completion"},
    {"question":"宗教","answer":["しゅうきょう"],"meaning":"religion; religious affiliation; belief; faith; creed, religious activity"},
    {"question":"宝","answer":["たから"],"meaning":"treasure"},
    {"question":"製造","answer":["せいぞう"],"meaning":"manufacture; production"},
    {"question":"実施","answer":["じっし"],"meaning":"enforcement; implementation; putting into practice; carrying out; operation; working (e.g. working parameters); enactment"},
    {"question":"家賃","answer":["やちん"],"meaning":"rent"},
    {"question":"製品","answer":["せいひん"],"meaning":"manufactured goods; finished goods; product"},
    {"question":"審判","answer":["しんぱん"],"meaning":"refereeing; trial; judgement; judgment; umpire; referee"},
    {"question":"裸","answer":["はだか"],"meaning":"naked; nude; bare"},
    {"question":"専攻","answer":["せんこう"],"meaning":"major subject; special study"},
    {"question":"装置","answer":["そうち"],"meaning":"equipment; installation; apparatus; device"},
    {"question":"裁判","answer":["さいばん"],"meaning":"trial; judgement; judgment"},
    {"question":"袖","answer":["そで"],"meaning":"sleeve, wing (of a stage, desk, gate, etc.)"},
    {"question":"衣服","answer":["いふく"],"meaning":"clothes"},
    {"question":"就く","answer":["つく"],"meaning":"to ascend (the throne); to accede, to take (seat, position, course, etc.); to assume, to start (on a journey); to commence; to depart, to study (under teacher); to be an apprentice"},
    {"question":"就職","answer":["しゅうしょく"],"meaning":"finding employment; getting a job"},
    {"question":"尻","answer":["しり","けつ"],"meaning":"buttocks; behind; rump; bottom, undersurface; bottom, last place; end, consequence, ass; arse; buttocks, rear; end"},
    {"question":"届く","answer":["とどく"],"meaning":"to reach; to arrive; to get through; to get at, to be attentive; to pay attention, to be delivered; to carry (e.g. sound)"},
    {"question":"屋根","answer":["やね"],"meaning":"roof"},
    {"question":"履く","answer":["はく"],"meaning":"to put on (or wear) lower-body clothing (i.e. pants, skirt, etc.); to put on (or wear) footwear, to affix a sword to one's hip, to affix a bowstring to a bow"},
    {"question":"岩","answer":["いわ"],"meaning":"rock; boulder, crag; cliff, anchor"},
    {"question":"衛星","answer":["えいせい"],"meaning":"satellite"},
    {"question":"嵐","answer":["あらし"],"meaning":"storm; tempest, difficulty; trouble"},
    {"question":"州","answer":["しゅう","す"],"meaning":"state; province; county; oblast; department (of ancient China), continent, dear, sandbank; sandbar"},
    {"question":"巣","answer":["す"],"meaning":"nest; rookery; breeding place; hive, den, haunt, (spider's) web"},
    {"question":"左右","answer":["さゆう"],"meaning":"left and right, influence; control; domination"},
    {"question":"行儀","answer":["ぎょうぎ"],"meaning":"manners; behavior; behaviour"},
    {"question":"航空","answer":["こうくう"],"meaning":"aviation; flying"},
    {"question":"希望","answer":["きぼう"],"meaning":"hope; wish; aspiration"},
    {"question":"舌","answer":["した"],"meaning":"tongue, tongue-like object; clapper (of a bell); talon (of a lock)"},
    {"question":"幅","answer":["はば"],"meaning":"width; breadth, freedom (e.g. of thought); latitude, gap; difference (e.g. in price); range (e.g. of voice), unit of measurement for cloth breadth (30-38 cm), scroll, counter for scrolls"},
    {"question":"至る","answer":["いたる"],"meaning":"to arrive at (e.g. a decision); to reach (a stage); to attain, to lead to (a place); to get to, to come; to arrive; to result in"},
    {"question":"自身","answer":["じしん"],"meaning":"by oneself; personally"},
    {"question":"年中","answer":["ねんじゅう"],"meaning":"whole year; all year round; throughout the year, always; all the time, middle class (of a nursery school, etc.)"},
    {"question":"年月","answer":["ねんげつ"],"meaning":"months and years"},
    {"question":"自慢","answer":["じまん"],"meaning":"pride; boast"},
    {"question":"腰","answer":["こし"],"meaning":"back; lower back; waist; hips; lumbar region, body (of hair, noodle, paper, etc.); resilience; spring, posture; position; pose; attitude"},
    {"question":"腐る","answer":["くさる"],"meaning":"to rot; to go bad; to decay; to spoil; to fester; to decompose; to turn sour (e.g. milk), to corrode; to weather; to crumble, to become useless; to blunt; to weaken (from lack of practice), to become depraved; to be degenerate; to be morally bankrupt; to be corrupt, to be depressed; to be dispirited; to feel discouraged; to feel down, indicates scorn or disdain for another's action, to lose a bet, to be drenched; to become sopping wet"},
    {"question":"脇","answer":["わき"],"meaning":"armpit; under one's arm; side; flank, beside; close to; near; by, aside; to the side; away; out of the way, off-track; off-topic, deuteragonist; supporting role, second verse (in a linked series of poems), side; edge; beside; besides; nearby, while (doing); in addition to; at the same time"},
    {"question":"胸","answer":["むね"],"meaning":"chest; breast, breasts; bosom; bust, heart, lungs, stomach, heart; mind; feelings"},
    {"question":"肩","answer":["かた"],"meaning":"shoulder"},
    {"question":"建設","answer":["けんせつ"],"meaning":"construction; establishment"},
    {"question":"弁当","answer":["べんとう"],"meaning":"bento; Japanese box lunch"},
    {"question":"引っ張る","answer":["ひっぱる"],"meaning":"to pull; to draw; to pull tight, to string (lines); to run (cable); to stretch, to pull towards oneself (e.g. someone's sleeve), to drag; to haul; to tow, to lead (e.g. one's followers), to take someone somewhere (e.g. a suspect to the police), to tempt into joining; to strongly invite to join, to delay; to prolong, to lengthen the pronunciation (of a word), to quote; to cite; to reference, to pull the ball, to wear; to put on"},
    {"question":"張る","answer":["はる"],"meaning":"to stick; to paste; to affix, to stretch; to spread; to strain; to tighten; to put up (tent), to form (e.g. ice on a pond), to fill; to swell, to stick out; to put; to slap, to be expensive, to keep a watch on; to be on the lookout, to become one tile away from completion, to span; to generate, to be prominently ...; to be persistently ..."},
    {"question":"影","answer":["かげ"],"meaning":"shadow; silhouette; figure; shape, reflection; image, ominous sign, light (stars, moon), trace; shadow (of one's former self)"},
    {"question":"影響","answer":["えいきょう"],"meaning":"influence; effect, to influence; to affect; to have an influence on; to impact; to have an effect on"},
    {"question":"従う","answer":["したがう"],"meaning":"to abide (by the rules); to obey; to follow; to accompany"},
    {"question":"微妙","answer":["びみょう"],"meaning":"delicate; subtle; sensitive, difficult; delicate (situation); complicated, doubtful; questionable; dicey; tricky, unspeakably wonderful; sublime; exquisite; marvelous"},
    {"question":"微笑む","answer":["ほほえむ"],"meaning":"to smile"},
    {"question":"徹夜","answer":["てつや"],"meaning":"all night; all-night vigil; sleepless night"},
    {"question":"徹底","answer":["てってい"],"meaning":"thoroughness; completeness; consistency, thorough enforcement; seeing to it that a policy, etc. is carried out without exception"},
    {"question":"肌","answer":["はだ"],"meaning":"skin, body (in the context of intimate bodily contact), surface; grain (e.g. of wood); texture, disposition; temperament; character; type"},
    {"question":"応じる","answer":["おうじる"],"meaning":"to respond; to satisfy; to accept; to comply with; to apply for"},
    {"question":"考慮","answer":["こうりょ"],"meaning":"consideration; taking into account"},
    {"question":"怠ける","answer":["なまける"],"meaning":"to be idle; to slacken, to neglect (e.g. one's work)"},
    {"question":"急激","answer":["きゅうげき"],"meaning":"sudden; precipitous; radical"},
    {"question":"怪我","answer":["けが"],"meaning":"injury (to animate object); hurt"},
    {"question":"恋","answer":["こい"],"meaning":"(romantic) love"},
    {"question":"恋人","answer":["こいびと"],"meaning":"lover; sweetheart"},
    {"question":"恩","answer":["おん"],"meaning":"favour; favor; obligation; debt of gratitude"},
    {"question":"翼","answer":["つばさ","よく"],"meaning":"wing, Chinese \"Wings\" constellation (one of the 28 mansions), counter for birds or bird wings"},
    {"question":"悩む","answer":["なやむ"],"meaning":"to be worried; to be troubled"},
    {"question":"悪魔","answer":["あくま"],"meaning":"devil; demon; fiend, Satan; the Devil, Māra; evil spirits or forces that hinder one's path to enlightenment"},
    {"question":"悲劇","answer":["ひげき"],"meaning":"tragedy; tragic drama; tragic play, tragedy; calamity; disaster"},
    {"question":"羽","answer":["はね"],"meaning":"feather; plume; down, wing, blade (of a fan, propeller, etc.), shuttlecock, counter for birds and rabbits, fifth degree (of the Japanese & Chinese pentatonic scale)"},
    {"question":"愉快","answer":["ゆかい"],"meaning":"pleasant; happy"},
    {"question":"意志","answer":["いし"],"meaning":"will; volition; intention; intent; determination"},
    {"question":"感謝","answer":["かんしゃ"],"meaning":"thanks; gratitude"},
    {"question":"態度","answer":["たいど"],"meaning":"attitude; manner; behaviour"},
    {"question":"慎重","answer":["しんちょう"],"meaning":"careful; cautious; prudent; discreet; deliberate"},
    {"question":"憲法","answer":["けんぽう"],"meaning":"constitution"},
    {"question":"成功","answer":["せいこう"],"meaning":"success; hit"},
    {"question":"成績","answer":["せいせき"],"meaning":"results; record; grades; marks"},
    {"question":"我々","answer":["われわれ"],"meaning":"we"},
    {"question":"我慢","answer":["がまん"],"meaning":"patience; endurance; perseverance; tolerance; self-control; self-denial"},
    {"question":"扱う","answer":["あつかう"],"meaning":"to deal with (a person); to treat; to handle; to take care of; to entertain, to deal with (a problem); to handle; to manage, to operate (e.g. a machine); to handle; to work, to deal in; to sell, to cover (a topic); to treat; to discuss; to take up, to treat A as B, to mediate (an argument), to be too much for one; to find unmanageable, to gossip"},
    {"question":"批判","answer":["ひはん"],"meaning":"criticism; judgement; judgment; comment"},
    {"question":"批評","answer":["ひひょう"],"meaning":"criticism; review; commentary"},
    {"question":"承知","answer":["しょうち"],"meaning":"knowledge; awareness, consent; acceptance; assent; admitting; compliance; agreement; acknowledgment; acknowledgement, forgiving; pardoning; excusing"},
    {"question":"義務","answer":["ぎむ"],"meaning":"duty; obligation; responsibility"},
    {"question":"罰する","answer":["ばっする"],"meaning":"to punish; to penalize; to penalise"},
    {"question":"投票","answer":["とうひょう"],"meaning":"voting; poll"},
    {"question":"抵抗","answer":["ていこう"],"meaning":"resistance; opposition; standing up to, reluctance; repulsion; repugnance, resistance; drag; friction, electrical resistance, resistor"},
    {"question":"繰り返す","answer":["くりかえす"],"meaning":"to repeat; to do something over again"},
    {"question":"拍手","answer":["はくしゅ"],"meaning":"clapping hands; applause, clapping one's hands in prayer (at a shrine)"},
    {"question":"拡大","answer":["かくだい"],"meaning":"magnification; enlargement; expansion; amplification"},
    {"question":"縦","answer":["たて"],"meaning":"the vertical; height, front-to-back; length, north-to-south, vertical (relationship); hierarchy, (weaving) warp"},
    {"question":"振る","answer":["ふる"],"meaning":"to wave; to shake; to swing, to sprinkle; to throw (dice), to cast (actor); to allocate (work), to turn down (somebody); to reject; to jilt; to dump, to abandon; to give up; to ruin, to add kana indicating a reading of a word, to slightly change headings; to change directions, to extract by broiling; to prepare an infusion of; to decoct, to carry with great vigor (e.g. a portable shrine), to bring up a topic; to lead to a topic, to replace; to substitute, to set up a joke for somebody else, assuming the air of ...; behaving like ..., to put on airs; to be self-important"},
    {"question":"掃除","answer":["そうじ"],"meaning":"cleaning; sweeping; dusting; scrubbing"},
    {"question":"掲示","answer":["けいじ"],"meaning":"notice; bulletin; post; posting; placard"},
    {"question":"描く","answer":["かく","えがく"],"meaning":"to draw; to paint; to sketch, to depict; to describe, to picture in one's mind; to imagine, to form a certain shape (e.g. path of an action, appearance of an object, etc.)"},
    {"question":"提出","answer":["ていしゅつ"],"meaning":"to present; to submit (e.g. a report or a thesis); to hand in; to file; to turn in, presentation; submission; filing"},
    {"question":"提案","answer":["ていあん"],"meaning":"proposal; proposition; suggestion"},
    {"question":"換える","answer":["かえる"],"meaning":"to replace, to exchange; to interchange, to substitute"},
    {"question":"握る","answer":["にぎる"],"meaning":"to clasp; to grasp; to grip; to clutch, to make (nigirizushi, rice ball, etc.); to form; to press into shape; to mold; to mould, to seize (power, etc.); to take hold of"},
    {"question":"握手","answer":["あくしゅ"],"meaning":"handshake"},
    {"question":"援助","answer":["えんじょ"],"meaning":"assistance; aid; support"},
    {"question":"縄","answer":["なわ"],"meaning":"rope; cord, policeman's rope"},
    {"question":"緊張","answer":["きんちょう"],"meaning":"tension; mental strain; nervousness"},
    {"question":"撃つ","answer":["うつ"],"meaning":"to shoot (at), to attack; to defeat; to destroy; to avenge"},
    {"question":"操作","answer":["そうさ"],"meaning":"operation; management; handling, manipulating to one's benefit"},
    {"question":"改善","answer":["かいぜん"],"meaning":"betterment; improvement, kaizen (Japanese business philosophy of continuous improvement)"},
    {"question":"攻撃","answer":["こうげき"],"meaning":"attack; strike; offensive, criticism; censure; denunciation; condemnation"},
    {"question":"政府","answer":["せいふ"],"meaning":"government; administration"},
    {"question":"故郷","answer":["こきょう","ふるさと"],"meaning":"home town; birthplace; native place; one's old home, ruins; historic remains"},
    {"question":"救う","answer":["すくう"],"meaning":"to rescue from; to help out of; to save"},
    {"question":"救助","answer":["きゅうじょ"],"meaning":"relief; aid; rescue"},
    {"question":"教授","answer":["きょうじゅ"],"meaning":"professor, teaching; instruction"},
    {"question":"綿","answer":["わた","めん"],"meaning":"cotton, cotton plant (Gossypium spp.), batting; wadding; padding"},
    {"question":"整理","answer":["せいり"],"meaning":"sorting; arrangement; organization; putting in order; adjustment; regulation, liquidation; settlement; consolidation; clearance (e.g. debt); paying off, retrenchment; curtailment; cutting down; disposal"},
    {"question":"敵","answer":["てき","かたき"],"meaning":"rival; opponent; adversary; competitor; enemy (esp. one with which there is longstanding enmity); foe, revenge, spouse, opponent; rival; adversary, menace; danger; threat; enemy"},
    {"question":"文句","answer":["もんく"],"meaning":"complaint; grumbling; objection, phrase; words; expression"},
    {"question":"新鮮","answer":["しんせん"],"meaning":"fresh"},
    {"question":"旗","answer":["はた"],"meaning":"flag"},
    {"question":"日中","answer":["にっちゅう"],"meaning":"daytime; during the day, Sino-Japanese"},
    {"question":"昇る","answer":["のぼる"],"meaning":"to ascend; to go up; to climb, to ascend (as a natural process, e.g. the sun); to rise, to go to (the capital), to be promoted, to add up to, to advance (in price), to swim up (a river); to sail up, to come up (on the agenda)"},
    {"question":"易しい","answer":["やさしい"],"meaning":"easy; plain; simple"},
    {"question":"是非","answer":["ぜひ"],"meaning":"certainly; without fail, right and wrong; pros and cons"},
    {"question":"維持","answer":["いじ"],"meaning":"maintenance; preservation; improvement"},
    {"question":"暖かい","answer":["あたたかい"],"meaning":"warm; mild; genial"},
    {"question":"替える","answer":["かえる"],"meaning":"to replace, to exchange; to interchange, to substitute"},
    {"question":"絶滅","answer":["ぜつめつ"],"meaning":"destruction; extinction"},
    {"question":"結論","answer":["けつろん"],"meaning":"conclusion"},
    {"question":"服装","answer":["ふくそう"],"meaning":"garments; attire"},
    {"question":"本人","answer":["ほんにん"],"meaning":"the person himself"},
    {"question":"結果","answer":["けっか"],"meaning":"result; consequence; outcome; effect, coming to fruition; bearing fruit"},
    {"question":"材料","answer":["ざいりょう"],"meaning":"ingredients; material, material (for a novel, experiment, etc.); subject matter; data, basis (for a decision); grounds; evidence, (market) factor"},
    {"question":"条件","answer":["じょうけん"],"meaning":"condition; conditions; term; terms; requirement; requirements"},
    {"question":"板","answer":["いた"],"meaning":"board; plank, sheet (of metal); plate (of glass); pane; slab, cutting board; chopping board, chef (esp. of high-end Japanese cuisine); cook, stage (i.e. at a theatre)"},
    {"question":"株","answer":["かぶ"],"meaning":"stock; share, stump, root; rootstock, strain (of bacteria, etc.), tradeable rank; goodwill, one's forte"},
    {"question":"根","answer":["ね","こん"],"meaning":"root (of a plant), root (of a tooth, hair, etc.); center (of a pimple, etc.), root (of all evil, etc.); source; origin; cause; basis, one's true nature, (fishing) reef, stick-to-itiveness; perseverance; persistence, radical (esp. one that tends to ionize easily), root, indriya (faculty of the body having a specific function, i.e. the sensory organs)"},
    {"question":"案内","answer":["あんない"],"meaning":"information; guidance; leading, to guide; to show (around); to conduct"},
    {"question":"桜","answer":["さくら"],"meaning":"cherry tree; cherry blossom, decoy; fake buyer; shill, hired applauder, horse meat"},
    {"question":"梅","answer":["うめ"],"meaning":"Japanese apricot (Prunus mume); Chinese plum, lowest (of a three-tier ranking system)"},
    {"question":"梅雨","answer":["つゆ"],"meaning":"rainy season (in Japan from early June to mid-July), rain during the rainy season"},
    {"question":"結局","answer":["けっきょく"],"meaning":"after all; eventually; in the end, conclusion; end, ending of a game of Go"},
    {"question":"椅子","answer":["いす"],"meaning":"chair; stool, post; office; position, traditional square chair with armrests and a torii-shaped back (used by the emperor, etc. during ceremonies)"},
    {"question":"結ぶ","answer":["むすぶ"],"meaning":"to tie; to bind; to link, to bear (fruit), to close (e.g. deal); to confirm; to conclude, to connect (two distant places), to close tightly; to purse (e.g. lips), to unite (with); to ally; to join hands"},
    {"question":"検査","answer":["けんさ"],"meaning":"inspection (e.g. customs, factory); examination; scan (e.g. MRI, PET, etc.)"},
    {"question":"検討","answer":["けんとう"],"meaning":"consideration; examination; investigation; study; scrutiny; discussion; analysis; review"},
    {"question":"模様","answer":["もよう"],"meaning":"pattern; figure; design, state; condition, conjecture of the current situation; the way it seems, model; pattern; example, indicates that that noun seems likely (e.g. rain or storm), framework (in go); territorial framework; moyo"},
    {"question":"機嫌","answer":["きげん"],"meaning":"humour; humor; temper; mood; spirits, safety; health; well-being; one's situation, in a good mood; in high spirits; happy; cheery; merry; chipper"},
    {"question":"経営","answer":["けいえい"],"meaning":"management; administration; operation; running (business); conducting"},
    {"question":"欠陥","answer":["けっかん"],"meaning":"defect; fault; deficiency; deformity, shortage; gap"},
    {"question":"次第","answer":["しだい"],"meaning":"depending on, as soon as; immediately (upon), in accordance with, order; program; programme; precedence, circumstances; course of events; reason"},
    {"question":"歓迎","answer":["かんげい"],"meaning":"welcome; reception"},
    {"question":"武器","answer":["ぶき"],"meaning":"weapon; arms; ordnance, weapon (something used to gain an advantage); asset"},
    {"question":"組織","answer":["そしき"],"meaning":"organization; organisation, structure; construction, tissue, system"},
    {"question":"比較","answer":["ひかく"],"meaning":"comparison"},
    {"question":"素晴らしい","answer":["すばらしい"],"meaning":"wonderful; splendid; magnificent"},
    {"question":"気に入る","answer":["きにいる"],"meaning":"to be pleased with; to suit"},
    {"question":"納得","answer":["なっとく"],"meaning":"consent; assent; agreement, understanding; comprehension; grasp"},
    {"question":"気温","answer":["きおん"],"meaning":"atmospheric temperature"},
    {"question":"水準","answer":["すいじゅん"],"meaning":"level; standard, water level"},
    {"question":"粗末","answer":["そまつ"],"meaning":"crude; rough; plain; humble; shabby"},
    {"question":"粗い","answer":["あらい"],"meaning":"coarse; rough"},
    {"question":"永遠","answer":["えいえん"],"meaning":"eternity; perpetuity; immortality; permanence"},
    {"question":"範囲","answer":["はんい"],"meaning":"extent; scope; sphere; range; span"},
    {"question":"汚染","answer":["おせん"],"meaning":"pollution; contamination"},
    {"question":"節約","answer":["せつやく"],"meaning":"economising; saving"},
    {"question":"管理","answer":["かんり"],"meaning":"control; management (e.g. of a business)"},
    {"question":"泉","answer":["いずみ"],"meaning":"spring; fountain"},
    {"question":"波","answer":["なみ"],"meaning":"wave, Poland"},
    {"question":"消防","answer":["しょうぼう"],"meaning":"fire fighting, fire department; fire brigade"},
    {"question":"涙","answer":["なみだ"],"meaning":"tear; tears; lachrymal secretion, sympathy"},
    {"question":"筋肉","answer":["きんにく"],"meaning":"muscle; sinew, sinewy meat"},
    {"question":"筋","answer":["すじ"],"meaning":"muscle; tendon; sinew, vein; artery, fiber; fibre; string, line; stripe; streak, reason; logic, plot; storyline, lineage; descent, school (e.g. of scholarship or arts), aptitude; talent, source (of information, etc.); circle; channel, well-informed person (in a transaction), logical move (in go, shogi, etc.), ninth vertical line, seam on a helmet, gristly fish paste (made of muscle, tendons, skin, etc.), social position; status, on (a river, road, etc.); along, counter for long thin things; counter for roads or blocks when giving directions, (Edo period) counter for hundreds of mon (obsolete unit of currency), muscle"},
    {"question":"清潔","answer":["せいけつ"],"meaning":"clean; hygienic; sanitary, pure; virtuous; immaculate"},
    {"question":"渋滞","answer":["じゅうたい"],"meaning":"congestion (e.g. traffic); delay; stagnation"},
    {"question":"減らす","answer":["へらす"],"meaning":"to abate; to decrease; to diminish; to shorten"},
    {"question":"減る","answer":["へる"],"meaning":"to decrease (in size or number); to diminish; to abate"},
    {"question":"渡す","answer":["わたす"],"meaning":"to ferry across (e.g. a river); to carry across; to traverse, to lay across; to build across, to hand over; to hand in; to pass; to give; to transfer"},
    {"question":"渡る","answer":["わたる"],"meaning":"to cross over; to go across, to extend; to cover; to range; to span"},
    {"question":"温度","answer":["おんど"],"meaning":"temperature"},
    {"question":"温暖","answer":["おんだん"],"meaning":"warm; mild; temperate; warmth"},
    {"question":"準備","answer":["じゅんび"],"meaning":"preparation; setup; arrangements; provision; reserve"},
    {"question":"溺れる","answer":["おぼれる"],"meaning":"to drown; to nearly drown; to sink below the surface (of water), to indulge in; to lose one's head over something; to wallow in"},
    {"question":"滞在","answer":["たいざい"],"meaning":"stay; sojourn"},
    {"question":"演奏","answer":["えんそう"],"meaning":"musical performance"},
    {"question":"笛","answer":["ふえ"],"meaning":"flute; fife; pipe; recorder; flageolet; shakuhachi; clarinet, whistle"},
    {"question":"激しい","answer":["はげしい"],"meaning":"violent; furious; tempestuous, extreme; intense; fierce; strong, fervent; vehement, incessant; relentless, precipitous; steep"},
    {"question":"火災","answer":["かさい"],"meaning":"conflagration; fire"},
    {"question":"立派","answer":["りっぱ"],"meaning":"splendid; fine; handsome; elegant; imposing; prominent, praiseworthy; creditable; worthy, legal; legitimate; lawful, undeniable (e.g. crime); indisputable; solid"},
    {"question":"穴","answer":["あな","けつ"],"meaning":"hole, deficit; shortage; missing person (in a team, meeting, etc.), vacancy; opening, flaw, profitable place (or item, etc.) not well known by others, upset victory (with a large payoff), pit (of a theater), hiding place, underbelly (of society, etc.), ass; arse; buttocks, rear; end, acupuncture point, hole; notch"},
    {"question":"炎","answer":["ほのお"],"meaning":"flame; blaze, flames (of intense emotion, e.g. love, jealousy, anger); passion, -itis (indicating an inflammatory disease)"},
    {"question":"無事","answer":["ぶじ"],"meaning":"safety; peace; quietness"},
    {"question":"無料","answer":["むりょう"],"meaning":"free; no charge"},
    {"question":"無視","answer":["むし"],"meaning":"disregarding; ignoring"},
    {"question":"無駄","answer":["むだ"],"meaning":"futility; uselessness; pointlessness"},
    {"question":"熱中する","answer":["ねっちゅうする"],"meaning":"become enthusiastic about; be full of enthusiasm for; be crazy about; be keen on; be absorbed in; be intent on; devote oneself to; give oneself up to; abandon oneself to; put one's heart into; go heart and soul into; be infatuated with; enthuse over; be hooked on; go in for in a big way; be nuts about"},
    {"question":"穏やか","answer":["おだやか"],"meaning":"calm; gentle; quiet"},
    {"question":"積極的","answer":["せっきょくてき"],"meaning":"positive; assertive; active; proactive; aggressive"},
    {"question":"穀物","answer":["こくもつ"],"meaning":"grain; cereal; corn"},
    {"question":"物価","answer":["ぶっか"],"meaning":"prices of commodities; prices (in general); cost-of-living"},
    {"question":"特徴","answer":["とくちょう"],"meaning":"feature; trait; characteristic; peculiarity; distinction"},
    {"question":"状態","answer":["じょうたい"],"meaning":"current status; condition; situation; circumstances; state"},
    {"question":"状況","answer":["じょうきょう"],"meaning":"state of affairs (around you); situation; circumstances"},
    {"question":"狂う","answer":["くるう"],"meaning":"to go mad, to get out of order; to go amiss"},
    {"question":"独り","answer":["ひとり"],"meaning":"one person, alone; unmarried; solitary"},
    {"question":"独特","answer":["どくとく"],"meaning":"peculiarity; uniqueness; characteristic"},
    {"question":"独立","answer":["どくりつ"],"meaning":"independence (e.g. Independence Day); self-support"},
    {"question":"独身","answer":["どくしん"],"meaning":"bachelorhood; single; unmarried; celibate"},
    {"question":"現象","answer":["げんしょう"],"meaning":"phenomenon"},
    {"question":"環境","answer":["かんきょう"],"meaning":"environment; circumstance"},
    {"question":"稼ぐ","answer":["かせぐ"],"meaning":"to earn (income); to make (money), to score (points, victory); to gain (time); to play (for time), to work hard (at one's job); to labor; to labour; to toil"},
    {"question":"生じる","answer":["しょうじる"],"meaning":"to produce; to yield; to cause, to result from; to arise; to be generated"},
    {"question":"生まれ","answer":["うまれ"],"meaning":"birth; birthplace, born in (country, month, imperial era, zodiac year, etc.)"},
    {"question":"申し訳","answer":["もうしわけ"],"meaning":"apology; excuse"},
    {"question":"畑","answer":["はた","はたけ"],"meaning":"field (for fruits, vegetables, etc.); cultivated land; vegetable plot; kitchen garden; plantation, field (of specialization); sphere; area, womb; birth; birthplace"},
    {"question":"異なる","answer":["ことなる"],"meaning":"to differ; to vary; to disagree"},
    {"question":"異常","answer":["いじょう"],"meaning":"strangeness; abnormality; disorder"},
    {"question":"症状","answer":["しょうじょう"],"meaning":"symptoms; condition"},
    {"question":"癖","answer":["くせ"],"meaning":"habit (often a bad habit, i.e. vice); tendency, peculiarity; idiosyncrasy; mannerism, crease; wrinkle; curl; kink"},
    {"question":"発展","answer":["はってん"],"meaning":"development; growth; advancement; unfurling, expansion; extension; enlargement, playing around; having an active sex life"},
    {"question":"皮","answer":["かわ"],"meaning":"skin; hide; pelt; fur, rind; peel; husk; bark, shell; sheath; wrapping, mask (hiding one's true nature); seeming"},
    {"question":"皿","answer":["さら"],"meaning":"plate; dish; platter; disc, serving; helping; course, kanji radical 108 (at the bottom)"},
    {"question":"監督","answer":["かんとく"],"meaning":"supervision; control; superintendence; direction, director; superintendent; supervisor; coach; foreman; manager; overseer; controller; boss"},
    {"question":"目標","answer":["もくひょう"],"meaning":"mark; sign; landmark; benchmark, mark; objective; target"},
    {"question":"目的","answer":["もくてき"],"meaning":"purpose; goal; aim; objective; intention"},
    {"question":"直接","answer":["ちょくせつ"],"meaning":"direct; immediate; personal; firsthand"},
    {"question":"稲","answer":["いね"],"meaning":"rice plant"},
    {"question":"真剣","answer":["しんけん"],"meaning":"seriousness; earnestness, real sword (as opposed to unsharpened or wooden practice weapon)"},
    {"question":"眺め","answer":["ながめ"],"meaning":"scene; view; prospect; outlook"},
    {"question":"睡眠","answer":["すいみん"],"meaning":"sleep"},
    {"question":"瞬間","answer":["しゅんかん"],"meaning":"moment; second; instant"},
    {"question":"秘密","answer":["ひみつ"],"meaning":"secret; secrecy; confidentiality; privacy, secret; mystery, esoteric teachings"},
    {"question":"禁煙","answer":["きんえん"],"meaning":"abstaining from smoking; quitting smoking, No Smoking!; Smoking Prohibited!"},
    {"question":"禁止","answer":["きんし"],"meaning":"prohibition; inhibition; ban"},
    {"question":"砂漠","answer":["さばく"],"meaning":"desert"},
    {"question":"祝う","answer":["いわう"],"meaning":"to congratulate; to celebrate; to observe (a festival)"},
    {"question":"礼儀","answer":["れいぎ"],"meaning":"manners; courtesy; etiquette"},
    {"question":"祝い","answer":["いわい"],"meaning":"congratulation; congratulations; celebration; festival; congratulatory gift"}
  ]
}